<testing>
<text file="SmallValid//a1.xml">
  <body>

Alright guys, you have to know we're kidding.  I don't think either of us are going to be wagging that war again any time soon.  Bass isn't even going to be there.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a10.xml">
  <body>

Lets wait till Monday to send to Toby.  Looks like it should be in both critical notices and balancing section.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a100.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, here is the latest list.  I just sent it to you since Randy and LD already have it.  We have
	a call into <NAME/> Stern about the columns and which ones to use (you probably already know the
	answer to that).  Thanks <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a101.xml">
  <body>

Joe,
I need some help on the schedule for September 20th.   <NAME/> Olinde is on vacation this day.   I intended to cover for him,  but I am now trading the dailies for Frontera.     I will not be able to cover the RT shift.

I know that you are working alot of days before then,  but I would appreciate your help.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a102.xml">
  <body>

Grier <NAME/> with El Paso Merchant Energy called - he's interested in the Trailblazer capacity.  His number is 713-420-5673.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a103.xml">
  <body>

Hi <NAME/>,


<NAME/> you please call this lady at TransCanada, Tracy in Gas Accounting at 402-505-8800.  She says we have a couple of term deals that have the incorrect TransCanada counterparty.  They are not deals in my region, so I thought it best to have you handle, as opposed to passing her around..

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a104.xml">
  <body>

Attached are copies of the PG&E Standstill Agreement (for reference) and the last extension that we did for the month of July (standstill expires on July 20).

I will be out of the office starting today and will not return until July 30. After we have finalized the terms of the extension with PG&E,  these are the forms that will need to be revised.  <NAME/>, if for any reason you need any help on this, please feel free to ask <NAME/> for assistance.  She is out today but will be in Friday and Monday.  Thanks.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a105.xml">
  <body>

I talked with <NAME/> Darveaux and there are some possible billing changes  coming that
	we need to discuss in the morning.

	1.  There may be a 10 day lag on pricing
	2.  The MPS imbalance volume will be taken out of the tiering denominator
		calculation. (as well as fuel)
	3.  We need to run a report to see how oftern (if at all) we have had imbalances on MPS contracts.

	Do you have any time Wed. morning?  What about 9:00 a.m. in my office?  If that
	doesn't work we can look at tomorrow afternoon.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a106.xml">
  <body>

Happy Birthday!
Sounds like a fun time.
I have a dentist appt out by the house at 4:00 pm so I will have to opt for dinner next week!
<NAME/> you have a fun night celebrating your ah? 28 birthday, right?
Call when you figure out what's good for you.  Wednesday looks best for me right now.

	<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a107.xml">
  <body>

Would you change the desk on deal 1064348 from Gulf2 to East TP1 please?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a108.xml">
  <body>

"Net Income" means consolidated gross revenues of Customer and other proper income credits, less all proper income charges, including taxes on income, all determined in accordance with GAAP.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a109.xml">
  <body>

Thurs at 530 would work great - See ya there 

PS I didn't make the masters yet but ...... soon? I'm talking to my brother who is having some rough times about doing another family triathlon together at a Delaware beach.  Of course I'd have to somehow find a bike to practice on - I haven't been on one since <NAME/> was born.  See ya Thurs.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a11.xml">
  <body>

Keoni,
I am not concerned with the improperly posted ATC's. I am concerned that our bids to relieve congestion were awarded but that the respective dollar value for those bids was incorrect. We have had problems in the past with misentry of our congestion management bids. However, in this case, the awarded congestion management bids look correct to me, and it appears that the CAISO published price is not appropriate for the amount of mws flowed. I would like to figure this out as soon as possible so that we can fix any problems that might exist on our end.

Please give me a call when you have a chance.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a110.xml">
  <body>

Okay, you asked for it....

The mind I love must have wild places, a tangled orchard where dark
                                  damsons drop in the heavy grass, an overgrown little wood, the chance of a
                                  snake or two, a pool that nobody's fathomed the depth of, and paths
                                  threaded with flowers planted by the mind.
                                  - - - <NAME/> Mansfield

I absolutely love this quote.  It manages to state, significantly more eloquently than myself, my own personal mantra of the last few years...I want to be pleasantly surprised.  Which is ultimately why I don't see it within my power in the near future to settle.  Maybe years down the road when desperation has set in I'll break down and throw myself at some sub-par individual, but let's hope it never gets to that point or if it does that I'm bordering on senile and just don't know any better.  

Anyway, I'm so glad we got to spend so much time together at <NAME/>'s wedding and I love hanging out with you Mom and Becka (sp?)...they crack me up.  If there's anything I can do to assist you with this wedding, let me know...even if you just need someone to run errands with or support your ideas.  I'd love to get together sometime this week for a drink, coffee, dinner, or whatever if you have any free time.  Maybe <NAME/> would be available as well?

Talk to you soon,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a111.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, MaryLou does NOT get differential pay.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a112.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I had to change <NAME/> to <NAME/> <NAME/> on your request.  We had to many people
	selecting <NAME/> and I need to evenly distribute the reviews.  If you have any concerns, please
	let me know.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a113.xml">
  <body>

Sarabeth,

Could you change the person that you send the Citizens Insurance Invoice to to the following:

Laynie East @ EB2363B

her phone number is 713-853-3131 and she will be paying the invoice.  If you have any questions, please call me at x30685.

Thanks,

<NAME/> <NAME/>
Manager, West Gas Origination
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a114.xml">
  <body>

I'll call Dari and have her put the rounded number in.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a115.xml">
  <body>

Bernice,

Please set up a new login for <NAME/> Kaniss for EOL stack manager.  He will be trading US East Power and US NorthAmerican Gas.  <NAME/> works for me on the East Power MidWest desk and will be training under me for the rest of this year.  All transactions under this login should go into EPMI MidWest risk book.  If you have any qestions, please call me at x 3-9684.  Thanks,

<NAME/> Sturm

p.s.  I'd like him to be able to login tomorrow a.m. if possible.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a116.xml">
  <body>

hello....long time no see.  how are y'all doing these days?

i'm actually writing bc i've misplaced em's phone number in london and wanted to give her a buzz.  do either of you have it on hand?  if so, could you please email it back to me.  thanks

em also mentioned something about NB in mid Sept...i'd love to see y'all if you decide to meet up with her.  

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a117.xml">
  <body>

Primary Receipt Point			Volume
012181  Wright SMA			35,000

Primary Delivery Point			Volume
020110  <NAME/> Massachusetts		1,000
020111  Leominster Massachusetts	1,000
020116	Revere Massachusetts		11,200
020191	<NAME/> Massachusetts		1,800
020285	Mendon Mass TIe Over		20,000

Total					35,000
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a118.xml">
  <body>

I give through paycheck withdrawal every month.

<NAME/> Sturm
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a119.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, October 4th works for me.  <NAME/> I think you are gone, so we need
	to involve Terry in this.  I am very open Thursday or Friday for a pre meeting.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a12.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, 

Attached is our term sheet in response to your request for bid.  I have also attached sample contract for your review.  We are waiting to hear from your credit guy to obtain some financial information.  Please call me with any questions or concerns.

Thanks,
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a120.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>'s game tonight is at 6:00pm not 7:30 as I previously thought. 

 <NAME/>'s game is at 8:00pm on Wednesday instead of 7:30.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a121.xml">
  <body>

Irena, I do not have MSN messenger.  I believe <NAME/> tried to set it up earlier, but I believe she said I needed an IT person to install.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a122.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
I put all the names in a hat...and you are the man...please revise the schedule and redistribute it with yourself attending the trip...
Enjoy!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a123.xml">
  <body>

Thought I would send this to you to approve.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a124.xml">
  <body>

I do not believe we can make a single point a division in this case.  There is a definition of division on sheet no. 102B which seems to say a point must be interconnected with other points to be a division.  I know we treat single points as divisions in certain other contracts, but I believe these were set up prior to 11/2/92 and are "grandfathered". I also don't believe we are obligated - or able - to extend Sec. 11 rights to new points.  Frazier, what's your reading of this?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a125.xml">
  <body>

Stacy, 

The customer has requested that we send them 2 executable, signed copies of this contract.  Could you have 2 executable copies of this contract prepared and sent down to me for signature?  I will have them sent to the customer.  Let me know if you have any questions.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a126.xml">
  <body>

I know, I know....I dropped off the face of the earth for a while.  I've actually been in <NAME/> all week for a Natural Gas Convention.  As for Labor Day weekend, I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to make it.  I'm leaving for S. Korea next Tuesday and don't get back until the weekend before Labor Day weekend.  So issue one is, will I have enough energy to make the trip?  The other issue is a friend's wedding in Park City that same weekend.  I'd feel bad skipping her wedding but still going on a trip.  So.....I was thinking maybe it'd be better all around if I came a different weekend.  Why don't you take a look at your calendar and let me know what other dates in September look good to you.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a127.xml">
  <body>

this is good stuff

----


Note: forwarded message attached.


__________________________________________________
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a128.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
Can we meet today and discuss the pros and cons of this order.
I will be available as soon as you are ready...
Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a129.xml">
  <body>

This is a trade with OIL-SPEC-HEDGE-NG (<NAME/> Lavorato's book) and <NAME/> Zufferli's book CAND-PWR-PR

CAND-PWR-PR buys from OIL-SPEC-HEDGE-NG Nymex Gas

Cal 03			38,500 MMBtu/day		$3.2978
Cal 04-Cal 05		35,000 MMBtu/day		$3.4482
Cal 06-Cal 10		40,000 MMBtu/day		$3.7369
Cal 11-Cal 15		18,500 MMBtu/Day		$4.2057

Please Confirm Receipt


<NAME/> Z
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a13.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> needs to be set up with a certificate for the Ercot Portal.    Is there a form I need to fill out for this?


<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a130.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Per <NAME/>, we've already sent our requests.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a131.xml">
  <body>

I inadvertently sent a draft without Section 4.7.  Please see the attached and disregard the previous. 

  
Regards,
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a132.xml">
  <body>

Here is a first pass at the customer letter.  Probably needs some work on more detail.

	
			 
	Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a133.xml">
  <body>

LLoyd,

I'm supposed to give a presentation to the Trader Track sometime this month and I forget when.   Do you have that schedule?  Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a134.xml">
  <body>

When: Monday, September 17, 2001 11:00 AM-11:30 AM (GMT-06:00) Central Time (US & Canada).
Where: 3112f - <NAME/>'s desk

*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a135.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
Would it make sense to press our EES/West Point guys to a decision?    We should express that we want to hire internally,  however,  we do have external candidates that we are considering.

The Reliant guy,  Ryan <NAME/>,   was a good interview and seems to have something positive to prove.   I believe that HR has some specific questions that they wish us to ask regarding his employment at Reliant.

Also,   EES is petitioning <NAME/> for me to let Watt's go right now.    I have indicated to Terry <NAME/> that mid July would be preferable due to our being already short staffed.    

Let me know your thoughts on this when you get the chance.    I will be out of the office for half day Friday and all day on Monday.

Thanks!

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a136.xml">
  <body>

FYI.  All four of you do not need to be there.  But I would like one from accounting
	and one from scheduling.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a137.xml">
  <body>

It's the same as the name, but with no spaces.


	DL-ETSGasControllers@enron.com

Please send us a test case. 

Thanks DS
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a138.xml">
  <body>

PG&E may have some scheduling jobs open in Bethesda, Maryland (just outside of DC).  Send your resume to this person and mention my name if you are interested.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a139.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

     Attached is my response to your RFP on behalf of Noresco.  As noted in our conversation earlier today, I apologize for the tardiness of my response.  I do hope that you will consider our proposals along with the other responses that you received.  If you have any questions, please feel free to call me at 713-853-0685.  

Sincerely,

<NAME/> <NAME/>
Manager, West Gas Origination
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a14.xml">
  <body>

Is this gty for long term business? Do you anticipate a master with this company?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a140.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> and <NAME/>, great update message.  Thanks for being proactive and putting
	this out for us.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a141.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>

I just checked the Tenn EBB and it does not appear that Boston Gas is releasing the Net 284 space to anyone.  I also just got off the phone with Ivy at Iroquois, she is the capacity release lady.  She said she didn't think that Boston Gas has been using this space at all.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a142.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I had to change one of your reviewers.  I changed <NAME/> to <NAME/>.  I also removed
	<NAME/> since he had been selected to many times.  I will visit with him though and get
	some feedback. 

	Please let me know if you have any questions.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a143.xml">
  <body>

In response to your inquiry regarding gas agreements with <NAME/>   we currently show no agreements with Tosco Refining Company.

Regards,
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a144.xml">
  <body>

Photo's of my little angel.

http://www.growingfamily.com/webnursery/babypage_view.asp?URLID=0U0X1E7K6M

http://hometown.aol.com/trogg522/myhomepage/index.html
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a145.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, we have established Monday afternoon after <NAME/> <NAME/>' staff
	meeting to meet and discuss:

		1.  TW Shipper Imbalance Status

		2.  OBA termination/Resolution 

	We will stay in the conference room on 13.

	Just wanted to let you know this is replacing our Tuesday morning meeting
	which was not working well since everyone moved.

	Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a146.xml">
  <body>

I am going to email you the changes I have in the subsidiary form. There are some nits included which should be fixed in JD's.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a147.xml">
  <body>

When: Monday, November 19, 2001 3:00 PM-4:00 PM (GMT-06:00) Central Time (US & Canada).
Where: <NAME/> South, 6th floor

*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a148.xml">
  <body>

Are you saying that the U.S. Producers are hedging their Canadian Production with U.S. counterparties as opposed to Canadian counterparties?  Or are the decisions being made in the U.S. and executed in Canada?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a149.xml">
  <body>

Courtney, Randy Janzen is out of the office until Tuesday.  Can we have him do this
	on Tuesday or do I need to have someone else run the spreadsheet?  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a15.xml">
  <body>

Please disregard the first email. I made one slight change.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a150.xml">
  <body>

Please set up and annuity for June where the TP3 book pays the New England book a total of $57,266

This will show up as a loss in TP3.

Let me know if you have any questions.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a151.xml">
  <body>

Hey buddy,

Out of curiosity, what all are you bringing with you to San <NAME/>?  I'm running into some problems in the area of cocktail dresses as I developed some noticeable tan lines from my trip.  Oh well, I guess they're not that big a deal right?  

Also, do you just want to swing by my complex Friday morning to pick me up?  I promise not to run too late.

Talk to you soon,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a152.xml">
  <body>

sounds good....i'd rather be useless a day at work, than miss a day over there....in the grand scheme of life.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a153.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
Frontera did agree to do the financial swap for tomorrow.   I am really excited about getting this product off.    I guess we need to follow up with the swap papers now.

Here are some things that we proposed to Frontera:

September 20th - I suggested selling October at $24.75.   This was a 10.72 heat rate.       I had to take off for an <NAME/> trip and <NAME/> took over for me in trying to get them to transact.
Power moved down,  but so did gas,   The heat rate was the same,  but they still didnt want to transact as power moved down to $24.75.    Power reached low of 10 heat rate for October recently - it is currently 10.2.

I suggested early this week in selling balance of the week at a 10.5  heat rate.   The dailies have been now liquidating as low as 8.9 hr.


August (late) - <NAME/> proposed selling 12.7  heat rate in September .   They didnt want to because they wanted to liquidate in the daily market.  This didnt work out.

On a daily basis,  Frontera has a problem making timely decisions.   For example,   I give them gas prices and daily prices.   They say that they would like to stay offline for the next day.   I tell them that I will bookout my option.   
They call back later and say that they would like to run.     Bids are now $2 less for my option and the prices they receive for their ramp up and onpeak schedule are horrible.

On Tuesday,   I suggested selling a $24 call option for October for  a $1.25 premium.    This would have at least brought in $23,000.   They werent interested in this idea.

I communicate my feelings on the market very early.   If they could react quicker,   I would smack the first bids that showed their faces,  including EOL.
I could have taken out 200mw's in a simultaneous trades several times over the last two weeks.


<NAME/> has some other instances that he would like to relay.   He will be sending another e-mail.


This relationship,  although not initially profitable,  has allowed us to develop other relationships that would not have otherwise been possible.   I dont really want to lose the job.   We are providing some outstanding support, in my opinion.

The thing that weakens our case is that Ercot is not providing the appropriate settlement details that would help illustrate our case on the OOM payments.
The settlements extract,  as I learned on my trip,  is key to explainnig this value.     The OOM value itself is well over $200k.

Good luck!

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a154.xml">
  <body>

unbelievable

hope the end is near - I'll try to avoid calling (I do know your number) until I see <NAME/> and <NAME/> back in <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a155.xml">
  <body>

Rajesh,

<NAME/> and <NAME/> and I talked today and agreed that Conditions of Use agreements for Dabhol, Oman, and possibly Abu Dhabi would be a good starting point. Let's talk with <NAME/> tomorrow morning <NAME/> time. Are you in the <NAME/> office in Dubai?

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a156.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I had a conversation with <NAME/> Davidson (SoCal) yesterday.  Things have been going smoothly,
	because SoCal has not been calling any OFO days.  She felt like we would not have an issue until
	spring and at that time, there is an expectation that SoCal could be calling more OFOs.  We agreed
	to continue talking, but that does not resolve the issue completely.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a157.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Could you send an electronic version of the latest RFP you sent out?  I am having some people help me internally and an electronic version would be helpful.  Let me know if you have any questions.

Thanks,
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a158.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
Cammi Mursch has asked for an e-mail from <NAME/> authorizing an extension.
Can we do this?

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a159.xml">
  <body>

FYI, I'm sure these are not in the system yet but will be soon.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a16.xml">
  <body>

I don't know if she has registered yet so I've come up with a few items that I think the baby will need.  Please share this humble list with the appropriate people.  I do work for a bankrupt company you know.

Item			Price
2002 Range Rover 	$64,896             http://www.edmunds.com/new/2002/landrover/rangerover/index.html
2002 Porsche Boxster	$50,000		http://www.edmunds.com/new/2002/porsche/boxster/index.html
<NAME/> Hatcher		$$$		http://www.eonline.com/Facts/People/Bio/0,128,19,00.html
Natilie Imbruglia		$$$$		http://www.eonline.com/Facts/People/Bio/0,128,67918,00.html
Toshiba Big Screen	$2,189		http://electronics.cnet.com/electronics/0-6342372-1304-7297512.html?tag=3Dpdtl-list
Harley Davidson		$21,000		http://www.harley-davidson.com/motorcycles/motorcycles_detail.jsp?PRODUCT%3C%3Eprd_id=3D432813&FOLDER%3C%3Efolder_id=3D440145&bmUID=3D1015517216967
Blue Wave Boat		$18,000		http://striperguide.tripod.com/bluewave.htm
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a160.xml">
  <body>

Hi <NAME/>
 
<NAME/> and I will be there on the 20th.  Thanks.  
Also, sorry for the delay on getting the $7.00 to you - its in the mail today.  Thanks again for everything.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a161.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, here is the draft we worked on today.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a162.xml">
  <body>

if you get this give me a call on my cell phone....it's 5:15 right now
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a163.xml">
  <body>

home number: 713-622-2788
cell number:    713-775-6472

tonight would be great...should be home no later than 7pm <NAME/> time

mailing address:	3805 W. Alabama #3308
		<NAME/>, TX 77027

can't wait to chat....there are some really cheap tickets to san diego right now....i'm getting the urge to jet set.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a164.xml">
  <body>

This is the new CAISO calculation for ancillary service charges.  Please look it over and let me know if you have any questions.
Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a165.xml">
  <body>

i'm a total dork....before my last trip to seattle i sent away for the visitor bureau's tourist packet...

anyway, i was looking through it this weekend and it turns out i actually have a coupon for the symphony.  nothing big, something like 10% off, but i'd just thought i'd let you know.

hope you had a great weekend and i'll talk to you soon,
<NAME/>

btw...i also have coupons for the IMAX and some other attractions.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a166.xml">
  <body>

The ST ercot book is long 30 mw's in the offpeak hours for Monday.    We would like to sell these mw's at a reasonable price that is left to your judgement.
If prices look to be potentially negative,  of course,  sell the mw's.

Give me a call if you have questions, preferrably before 10 pm.


Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a167.xml">
  <body>

I have created deal 1150179 to cover this supply.  

<NAME/> - Please see that this gets pathed in MOPS and POPS and let <NAME/> know when completed.

Thanks.

D
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a168.xml">
  <body>

Lou,

I am still here but I am unable to give out quotes at this time.  Please accept my apologies and I will be in touch once things are straightened out around here.  

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a169.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I understand you were covering for <NAME/> Adams while she was on vacation.
	Did we have the proper coverage to get CMS allocated volumes in GVA reviewed
	as we needed.  Just wanted to follow up.  I would be glad to visit with you about
	this if we need.

	Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a17.xml">
  <body>

Here is my little angel.

http://hometown.aol.com/trogg522/myhomepage/index.html

http://www.growingfamily.com/webnursery/babypage_view.asp?URLID=0U0X1E7K6M

The first web site is my aol homepage and some people have a hard time pulling this one up.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a170.xml">
  <body>

Hey girl, I'm trying to print this document....is this something you scanned?  Why don't you fax it to me real quick and I'll sign immediately!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a171.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, sorry I am so late in sending this back.  Looks great to me.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a172.xml">
  <body>

They keep calling.  What do we need to do right now to do the Amgen blend and extend, either paper work or additional collateral?  Let me know soon.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a173.xml">
  <body>

I don't know if she has registered yet so I've come up with a few items that I think the baby will need.  Please share this humble list with the appropriate people.  I do work for a bankrupt company you know.

Item			Price
2002 Range Rover 	$64,896             http://www.edmunds.com/new/2002/landrover/rangerover/index.html
2002 Porsche Boxster	$50,000		http://www.edmunds.com/new/2002/porsche/boxster/index.html
<NAME/> Hatcher		$$$		http://www.eonline.com/Facts/People/Bio/0,128,19,00.html
Natilie Imbruglia		$$$$		http://www.eonline.com/Facts/People/Bio/0,128,67918,00.html
Toshiba Big Screen	$2,189		http://electronics.cnet.com/electronics/0-6342372-1304-7297512.html?tag=3Dpdtl-list
Harley Davidson		$21,000		http://www.harley-davidson.com/motorcycles/motorcycles_detail.jsp?PRODUCT%3C%3Eprd_id=3D432813&FOLDER%3C%3Efolder_id=3D440145&bmUID=3D1015517216967
Blue Wave Boat		$18,000		http://striperguide.tripod.com/bluewave.htm
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a174.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, thanks for the update.  Please let me know when you have info on the other information and the
	status of November.  I appreciate all your help. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a175.xml">
  <body>

Group-

We are currently owed money by CERS (approximately $100,000). We need to net this to a zero by Friday. It is very important that each of you call CERS and purchase energy from them to net this position out. Otherwise--we will see a loss of $100,000. Let's make this problem go away.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a176.xml">
  <body>

"....also, some annoying requests- katy forgot all the
minutemade frozen limeade she'd promised to bring for our Eagles marg party,
and the jerky from dad - suspiciously, she remembered my pocket-sized
neosporin tube......but anyways, it would be FABULOUS if you and lisa could
each cart over 3-4 tubes of the limeade wrapped in plastic
(carry-on....obviously could be ugly in non-pressurized cabin in suitcase!)
doesn't matter if thaws, but will need approx 7-10 tubes for the
festivities, plus, dad has that great turkey jerky from NB to send
along...."

Fear not, I have the turkey jerky.

Address...118 Portland Road (the postcode is W11 and the tube stop is Holland Park)

Phone #...011 44 2072 43 1926 (this is with the country code so I'm not sure exactly what you dial in London, I 							know you have to knock off the 011 and possibly the 44)

If you end up taking the tube you'll walk out of the tube station and take an immediate left.  Walk roughly two blocks and then take another right onto Portland Road.  There will be a pizza place right on the corner.  You'll walk all the way down Portland road until it looks like the road ends in a cul-de-sac.  The roads actually continues on the other side of a little bricked area with benches (a place called <NAME/>'s Wine Bar will be on your immediate left).  <NAME/>'s flat is in the row of flats to your right and the number is on the door (which if I remember correctly is blue).

See you there,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a177.xml">
  <body>

hey lisa....

what's the scoop with tasters tonight....time and location?

i think i'll try to come, even if it's just for a quick drink with the gang.

see you soon,
susan
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a178.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, 

We need to talk about the ability of ENA to continue its the current role as agent of Tenaska IV.

1)  Since the end on November, ENA has not been able to complete gas trading transactions.  We cannot find any counterparties to trade physical gas in Texas.  This, of course, is due to the bankruptcy.  As a result, we are not able to sale Tenaska's excess fuel.  We did contact Brazos to ask if they would buy a portion of the gas at a Gas Daily price, but they do not want it (gas daily pricing has been below the firm contract price for a while).  In December, we had to cut 10,000/day from the 7th through the 27th.  For January, we haven't had to cut yet, but I am sure that the pipe will ask us to do this in the near future.

2)  For November activity (which was settled in Dec), ENA owes Tenaska IV for the excess supply that we sold.  However, due to the bankruptcy, we could not make payments out.  ENA could not pay the suppliers or the pipeline.  <NAME/> Armstrong paid the counterparties directly.  I think that he should continue to do this for Dec and Jan.  We should not transfer any funds from Tenaska IV to ENA.

I don't know how <NAME/>'s ownership in the plant factors out in the bankruptcy preceding.  But we need to determine how to go forward with the fuel management.

Please give me a call or e-mail me.  We can get together sometime Thurs or Fri morning.

D
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a179.xml">
  <body>

I applied for the Origination - Wholesale position, job #1154 on the job posting board.  I would like to have the attached resume sent to the hiring manager as well please.

Please let me know if you have any comments or questions.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a18.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I wanted to see if I could get the PAA in for <NAME/>.  I think she did a very good job on the
	Transwestern meeting and I would like to recognize her for that.  If you approve, then I will
	send to <NAME/> to fill out the appropriate information.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a180.xml">
  <body>

Meoldy and <NAME/>, thank you for your help on this matter.  It was very important to us to have Outlook until
	11:00 p.m.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a181.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> and <NAME/>, I thought you both would be interested in seeing the attached.  This document
	came out of the meeting yesterday on Bushton.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a182.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

I am very interested in supplying your gas and plan on responding to your request for qualification.  If there is anything else that you need in the meantime, please give me a call.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
713-853-0685
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a183.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

I just got off of the phone with my credit guy - He says that most of the people on this list are not public companies.  It would be very helpful and will expedite the process if you could get the latest audited financial statements, with notes, from each of these companies.  With the PG&E thing, credit is swamped, but, if I had the info in hand, I could push our cause.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a184.xml">
  <body>

Please restore the below referenced file as requested.  If you have any questions, please
	call me at ext. 3-7637.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a185.xml">
  <body>

Group,

Also on Saturday morning...Enpower will be down from 5 AM to 7 AM.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a186.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
I just received this from <NAME/>.   I dont want to cause any double coverage by HR, so you might want to check with <NAME/>.
Thanks!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a187.xml">
  <body>

Getting warmer.  Could you send me an email with a brief description of how you see us marketing their energy.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a188.xml">
  <body>

Just <NAME/> and I chatting with Shemin.  We tried calling Dominion's Bankruptcy counsel, outside counsel (which is seperate), and in house counsel and couldn't get anyone.  I believe Shemin has a much better idea though.  BUT, I think its important to note that those producer agreements are Enfolio contracts.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a189.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

I have a few questions regarding the emminent implementation of the new target pricing mechanism.
1. Does uninstructed energy still get paid (if not, we cannot hedge financials)
2. The CISO Table 1. lists an unintended consequence as " Target price may be manipulated due to no obligation to deliver"
	Why is there no obligation to deliver?
3. Is there still a load deviation penalty? Or would that be considered seperately?

Thanks for the help.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a19.xml">
  <body>

Hi <NAME/>

You will want to liquidate the June Exotic Options today (using the valuation spreadsheet- Basis Pipe Options 2001.xls) as well as update the Option P&L file to account for the June Exotic option's value you calculate.  You will actually roll-over the Options P&L tomorrow, after you finalize the 31st's P&L (the final P&L file will include any Prior Month Adjustments as well as broker fees).  

You will update the Basis Pipe Options 2001.xls when the actual published indexes come out...so that will most likely be Monday.  At that point you can send the file to <NAME/> <NAME/> in it's final version.

If you have any other questions just come by and get me and we'll go over them.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a190.xml">
  <body>

Summary:  TDC Energy Corporation is requesting payment of $203,196.00 from ENA for post-petition gas that flowed in the month of December 2001 (sitara deal #1143983).  TDC stated that it would "file a claim for administrative expenses in the bankruptcy court in New York and seek all other necessary relief against ENA" if ENA did not remit payment by the close of business Feb 22, 2002.  Based on the information in this email it appears that ENA should pay TDC $203,196.00.  

<NAME/>, <NAME/>, Question:  I have not contacted TDC to determine if they have filed a claim with the court.  Would that have any impact on making a payment to TDC?  Should I contact TDC?


Calculation of Post-Petition Payment using Dec 3 as Post-Petition day
Gas scheduled Dec 3-24, 26-31 = 28 days, volume = 3,000 dth per day
28 x 3,000 x $2.419 = $203,196.00
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a191.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I was in the office for October 1 - 15th.   Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a192.xml">
  <body>

I just realized that I hadn't emailed you yet...shame on me.

Em and I (yes, it was just the two of us in NB...oh the shame) tried to call you on New Year's <NAME/>, but you had already checked out of your room and I assume were staying with Priyah (I know I butchered that) whose last name I do not know.  Anyway, I did talk to your Mom the day you arrived in Madras and knew you were there safe and sound w/ a new friend too boot!

<NAME/> you're doing okay and starting to adjust to the new surroundings.  Email me when you get a chance and let me know all about your trip.

Good Luck and talk to you soon,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a193.xml">
  <body>

Though tyou would find this interesting.  You might want to get added to this email list.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a194.xml">
  <body>

Yesterday I asked you how to go about paying an invoice from Peoples Energy for $1,380.44.  The charges are for a license fee, a customer service, and an outstanding balance of $983.75.  I found out this morning that we are using this system to do nominations for Enovate.  <NAME/> Boyt said he thought the <NAME/> people managing the Enovate deal are <NAME/> Jenkins and J.O. Pagan.  Should I forward this invoice to <NAME/> or J.O.?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a195.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
I am planning on attending this settlements deal;  we plan on meeting <NAME/> Patterson there.
<NAME/>
[Forney, <NAME/> M.] I am planning on attending
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a196.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Attached is the legal opinion.  <NAME/> Shackleton will be the attorney we
meet with on your changes and she is available all Wednesday afternoon.
Do you want to say 1:30 your time, 3:30 ours?  Please confirm and I will
set everything up with <NAME/>.

Thanks,
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a197.xml">
  <body>

Reliant should receive a payment of $10,000.00 today which will give us a cash balance of $60,820.00.

Have a good weekend.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a198.xml">
  <body>

Thanks for your call, yes the T letter is done and returned to Alagasco.  There is one deal still under the agreement that will die in October.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a199.xml">
  <body>

Group,
We have purchased 50 mws from LV Cogen for HE 8, HE 9 and HE 10 at $35.  We will need to buy transmission from NEVP from Nevada system to Mead 230 and then into the CAISO for HE 8 thru HE 10.  This energy can go towards the ST-CALI and ST-WBOM short in SP-15. I will do enpower for these deals when I arrive in the morning. Remember to give NEVP 2 hours of notice-maybe even 2 and a half...Please call me with any questions.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a2.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> (team leader),

I'll be unavailable to work on the skit video this Thurs (8/9) thru Mon (8/13) as I will be in Pennsylvania on vacation.  I have plenty of time this tues or wed after trading or next Tues - Thurs after trading...let me know.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a20.xml">
  <body>

When is the interview date at <NAME/> Laurier, Guelph and Waterloo?

Can they all be put on at the same time, either on or off-campus?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a200.xml">
  <body>

Cute little bugger.  <NAME/> Goodell said forget the Salt Lake City thing.  He said <NAME/> is paving the way for him with <NAME/> <NAME/>.  I don't know him.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a201.xml">
  <body>

One more time.  
We have also bought HE 21 and HE 22 from the APX.  We bought 20 mws at $32 for HE 21 and 23 mws at $30 for HE 22.
No more messages.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a202.xml">
  <body>

Thanks for asking -   things are still pretty tough here, but  I determined to make it work.         I am a Director now - would your management be concerned about that?-  just curious.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a203.xml">
  <body>

Huntman,

Any truth to the rumor about <NAME/> leaving the group (not the company)?

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a204.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> Leahey is going to help print contracts from live-link.  She is from the local Andrews & Kurth office.  I have set her up at <NAME/> Gomez's desk and she is using my id to print contracts.

She shouldn't need anything but if she does please help her. 

Thanks.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a205.xml">
  <body>

Hi Herb,

<NAME/> Bowler had actually given me your name and email address a little while back and thought it would be a good idea for me to drop you a line.  I have been working with <NAME/> for a couple weeks at <NAME/> and, upon learning that I was in the midst of job hunting, he suggested I contact you.  For the last year I served as an assistant trader on the West Natural Gas Desk (Wholesale).  For various reasons I chose to decline an offer in February with the newly formed UBSW Energy and am currently still working for <NAME/>.  I'm attaching a copy of my resume to give you a better idea of my background and experience.  If you know of any opportunities that seem like possible "good fits" I would very much appreciate hearing about them.

 

Thank you,
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a206.xml">
  <body>

victor,

take a look and fill people as you see best.  this is only preliminary so you will have a 
chance to revise if you change your mind.

thanks,

scott
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a207.xml">
  <body>

Did either one of you guys work on the APEA (American Public Energy Agency) gas prepay deal?  I think it was done in 1999 and Laird Dyer worked on it.  We are changing one of the counterparties and delivery points so we are going to need to amend some of the documents.  I know you two are going to fight over this so as soon as the dust settles, let me know who wins!

Thanks, 

<NAME/>

Call me if you have questions or don't know what deal I am talking about.  I have copies of some of the documents so they may be helpful.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a208.xml">
  <body>

so i'm back at home w/ the folks...i don't see this lasting too long.  mom woke me up this morning to see if i needed to get up and start getting ready...JEEZ....she said she'd heard my alarm going off.  you know how big i am on the snooze button.  anyway, i think we're going to have to have a chat tonight about "boundaries".  Ha.

in regards to enron, i still know nothing concrete.  hopefully by the end of the week we should now something w/ actual facts and figures.  

seattle was a really good trip...hoping to know more next week on that as well.  

talk to you soon,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a209.xml">
  <body>

Due to the relatively weak real-time market during morning hours, we wanted to communicate a strategy for dec. bidding or buying-back generation that you've sold forward.  We want to stress that this is a relatively short-term strategy.  As the weather turns cold during the late-<NAME/> and Winter months, the morning hours actually trade at a premium on the real-time market.

Lately, HE1-10 have been very weak real-time, ranging between $25 and $40.  We have two strategies that we would like to suggest:
Group,
We have two important items regarding the services and asset management side of our business.

First,
The CAISO has been calling repeatedly regarding outages.  We will continue to call the CAISO for every outage (including when Black Hills goes down 200 kWh).  <NAME/> has worked closely with the CAISO regarding their new tariff and her information appears below.  It is very important that we do not expose ourselves to charges by not notifying the CAISO of an outage.

Second,
We will be working with the generators to execute buy-backs or supplemental dec. bids when market conditions warrant.  <NAME/> has written an email to the generators also detailed below.  <NAME/> and <NAME/> will be contacting the generators over the next few days to review this email with them.  Afterwards the Real-Time group will contact the generators and initiate one of the two strategies when profitable.  Real-Time will retain 50% of the profits over the generator's day ahead profits.  Please let me know if you have any questions or feedback.

Thanks,

<NAME/>


__________________________________________________________________________

I have reviewed documents from the ISO's website regarding forced outages as they relate to the June 19 FERC order and concluded the following: 

(1) During a System Emergency, a penalty based on twice the highest price paid for energy in the hour could be assessed if the Participating Generator does not notify the ISO of the outage within the operating hour of the outage, and 

(2) During a Non-System Emergency, a generator could be assessed a penalty if it fails to report the forced outage within the operating hour. 

If you have any questions at all, I can be reached at extension 7733.  

Thanks,
<NAME/>

__________________________________________________________________________

1.  Decremental Supplemental Bids
We can submit dec. bids to the ISO at a price below your cost to generate.  Basically, we would be letting the ISO know that we're willing to reduce generation and actually buy the mw's from the ISO to cover the prescheduled quantity.  You are still paid the day-ahead price for the day-ahead quantity, but instead of generating it, you would be buying it from the ISO.  For example, if your cost to generate is $40, and you sell day-ahead for $50, you make $10/MWh.  If the ISO takes the decremental bid, and the price is $30, then you make $20/MWh.   

Advantages - A relatively large upside, the price the ISO charges could actually go negative, as large as negative $91.87.  Also, you would actually be buying from the ISO, as opposed to selling to the ISO and being subject to credit risk.

Disadvantages - Ten minute dispatch.  When we submit decremental bids, the ISO has the option to either reduce or increase output of the unit every 10 minutes.  In addition to the physical problems this might create, the settlements statement you receive might be relatively elaborate and possibly difficult to follow.

2.  Buying-Back Blocks in the Bi-Lateral Market:
This strategy calls for our real-time traders to buy blocks of energy in the bi-lateral market for below your cost to generate.  This would call for you to reduce your generation, and the energy we buy-back in the real-time market would be used to fill your prescheduled quantity.  Once again, you are still paid the day-ahead price for the day-ahead quantity, but instead of generating it, you would be buying it at the price paid to buy-back the energy.   As in the previous example, if your cost to generate is $40, and you sell day-ahead for $50, you make $10/MWh.  If we can buy-back the energy for a price of $30, then you make $20/MWh.   Additionally, if we do buy-back the energy, we will need to simultaneously submit incremental supplemental bids to the ISO to remain compliant with the FERC order.  Then, if the ISO takes the incremental bid, you can generate the power and sell for additional profit. 

Advantages - No 10 minute dispatch (unless a supplemental bid is accepted).  You would know exactly when and for how long the unit would be down or reduced.  Also, the settlements statements would be relatively easy to manage.

Disadvantage - Not as large of an up-side as decremental bidding.

At this point in time we would encourage you to start with the strategy #2, buying-back blocks of energy in the bi-lateral market.  Once you and our real-time traders get comfortable with the operations of the strategy, then we should move forward and start submitting decremental supplemental bids to the ISO.  We propose a 50/50 profit split, above your day-ahead profit, earned from either of these two strategies.

If you have any questions or comments please call myself or <NAME/> <NAME/>.

<NAME/> Cocke
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a21.xml">
  <body>

Further to our conversation, please see my address below.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a210.xml">
  <body>

This was intended for the other <NAME/> <NAME/>.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a211.xml">
  <body>

derek can you forward me the e-mail for the management conference?  my e-mail puked and deleted everything in my inbox.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a212.xml">
  <body>

Please disregard my previous email concerning <NAME/>.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a213.xml">
  <body>

In the interest of moving things forward, it would help if you could provide the following info:

1. Hand-marked copy of the portions of the current contract which need to be changed.

2. A brief description of the new deal, especially the index language.

I know VEPCO may be preparing a first draft, but I think it would be good to get some focus ahead of time.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a214.xml">
  <body>

I sent this from home Tuesday night.  I'm sending it again because the phone service at my apartment complex is out due to construction so I can't tell if you received it.

<NAME/>
cg
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a215.xml">
  <body>

The internet address for the Ercot Portal:

https://portla.ercot.com
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a216.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Please book the following accrual origination from grigsby's book to myself and <NAME/> <NAME/> ( 50% each):

June 2001	$9,566.58
July 2001	$5,706.52
Aug 2001	$7,736.97

Also, are you the one that I need to inform of what to pay <NAME/> Cogan?  And if so, what months and amounts have we paid him?

I will have september ready today or tomarrow and October ready by the 10th which will be our standard procedure.  Let me know if you have any questions.

thanks,

<NAME/>

ps  attached are the supporting spreadsheets
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a217.xml">
  <body>

Hi team.  I'm going to set myself up as the Navigator administrator for <NAME/> North America unless someone else wants to do it.  We use Navigator for activity on Columbia Gas, Columbia Gulf, Crossroads, and KO Transmission.  I think we also use Navigator to download the invoices.

I'm going to kill all the ID's shown below except mine.  Should I set up anyone else with an ID?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a218.xml">
  <body>

I did submit a request via "e Request" - #83213.  I didn't know if you wanted to assign other people to do this and I don't know HOW you would do that either.  I just asked for everything to cover all the bases.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a219.xml">
  <body>

I don't have their financials but lets get started on what we can get started with. I am not expecting to do financial swaps in the immediate term but I would like to be preparted when we are ready.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a22.xml">
  <body>

I forwarded this to Joe Parks - we both work for <NAME/> McMichael.  I believe this is something he is monitoring.  Let me know if you have more questions.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a220.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, please coordinate with <NAME/> a time <NAME/>, <NAME/> and I can talk about the 
	flowing gas documents no accessible to customers.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a221.xml">
  <body>

Please give <NAME/> Townsend, <NAME/> Goodell, and myself  the ability to trade the physical Canadian products.  We need to be able to see them on EOL.  

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a222.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> called <NAME/> about someone wanting us to cancel a contract then <NAME/> said there are still lots of producers putting gas on our contracts.  I was working on something else and I just asked <NAME/> to send me a worksheet of what he was talking about.  <NAME/> actually called <NAME/>.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a223.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> Gaskill and I will do it.

Does the audience understand the basics of natural gas?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a224.xml">
  <body>

Those dates are fine.  Of course I am sending this to you on the morning of the 19th so maybe you are already here.  I will be your contact.  We are at 1200 17th St. Suite 2750.  the office is  in the process of being subdivided so it will be easiest if you come by and I show you what we are doing.

Call me if you need anything at 303-575-6473.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a225.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
Could you sign me up for the bus pass. I am selling my car and no longer need the parking. 
Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a226.xml">
  <body>

Ok my dear....you just tell me when a good time is for me to visit and we'll go from there.  i got your x-mas present last night.  thank you very much, i'm anxious to start reading it.

if you do check email today, give me a shout back.  we can have an old fashioned email chat.  i'm worried about you mo.  i've been praying for you, for all that you're struggling with...but i'm stepping it up double time.  please don't completely retreat inside yourself right now...that doesn't mean you need to talk to me, but talk to someone.

love, 
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a227.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, please see my answers in red.  Sounds like you had a great meeting.  Let me know if
	you need any other info.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a228.xml">
  <body>

1.  <NAME/> Broderson  (770) 792-1962 (headhunter) is working on a postion for a trading/marketing company located in Dallas.

2.  <NAME/> Marino  (212) 704 2156  (headhunter) is working on a position in marketing/trading for Constellation energy.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a229.xml">
  <body>

Having visions is a guy thing you know.  I just thought Nanny <NAME/> would be good at teaching little <NAME/> about acting and Nanny Natilie (huba huba huba) could teach the little sucker how to sing.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a23.xml">
  <body>

I plan on being in both days let me know what works best for you.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a230.xml">
  <body>

The person at Select Nat Gas interested in the Trailblazer capacity is <NAME/> Schultz, phone number 303-797-3388.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a231.xml">
  <body>

I can play the 9:00 game and may be able to stay for the 11:00.

ds
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a232.xml">
  <body>

Definitely...to begin with he should be <NAME/> Mier.
Let me know what you need...

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a233.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> and Raetta, could you touch base with <NAME/> and see if you can help
	her out.  If not, then let's get together.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a234.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> and everyone, I think the directory is i:\canadian\energy service\integrated solutions\counterparty talks.xls
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a235.xml">
  <body>

Delaine Kurth with Oneok called today and wanted an OBA at the (Skellytown) Cargray
	Plant (POI 8442) effective 1/1/2002.  

	After talking with <NAME/>, I told her that we would draft an OBA on Wednesday with Month
	to Month cash out language in it.  She said to send her the contract and she will run the
	traps.  She was not excited about the monthly cash out requirement. I told her if we could
	come to agreement we would make it effective 1/1/2002.  If we could not come to agreement,
	we would continue the same methodology as we have today, which is Oneok picks one of the
	transportation contracts at the Cargray tailgate to take any variances.

	<NAME/>, per our conversation, please draft an OBA to send to Oneok.  

	If anyone has any other thoughts or comments on preparing this OBA, please let <NAME/> or
	I know.  

	Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a236.xml">
  <body>

I know I've thoroughly enjoyed all the commentary.  I can honestly say, I think this is the first time I've been invited to an Aggie happy hour....and to that end, kudos to all those who opted out of <NAME/>'s Boat...you now may be forced to deal with a longhorn interloper.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a237.xml">
  <body>

Hey there team.  We are starting to focus on Dominion pipeline and I need your help explaining the process to Shemin.  I would like to set up a meeting with <NAME/>, <NAME/>, Shemin, <NAME/> as soon as possible.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a238.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

What is the status of this document?  Customer is asking for it.  Please let me know -

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a239.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

I just received this from our client rep detailing their position.
As expected they are treating the Stage 1 as ending at 11:32 rather than HE 23 as stated on May 31 in both their website and on their message net.  
I would like to get FERC's position on this if necessary.  If it is $91.87 rather than $108.49 as indicated in the FERC order, we will use that as a cap as soon as FERC (or you) recommends it.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a24.xml">
  <body>

Did she show you her tatoo?

I need to be back in <NAME/> by 2:00 PM.  I'm thinking about driving myself.  Your the boss, what do you think?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a240.xml">
  <body>

I still don't have access to West (deal 1198936).  I'm almost positive I entered this deal and I thought I entered it as a Central Desk deal.  When I book my deals on Trunkline for April, should I use Central?  We will be serving the Midland Cogeneration deal #340362 for April.

I also didn't request access for ENA Upstream but <NAME/> Kelly should be able to take care of that.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a241.xml">
  <body>

I don't have a need for traders here in Calgary now.  I don't have a softcopy of the application.  He should think about Harvard and MIT
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a242.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> Thurston

State Coverage

<NAME/>
<NAME/>

<NAME/> Customers

Nicor Gas Company
Northern Indiana Gas Company
<NAME/>
<NAME/>
Illinois Power

Customers Unwilling to Transact due to Credit Concerns

Nicor - no financial deals--will continue to transact on physical deals
Proliance - will buy from ENA--will not sell to ENA
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a243.xml">
  <body>

Group,

Two totally different issues for you.

First:  When scheduling transmission on Portland General Electric from <NAME/> Day to Malin we MUST use deal #146517, we MUST make the price zero.  We extend this deal in scheduling and change the delivery points.  We then make an annuity to ST-NW for losses.  Easy.

Second: For the third time in two weeks the behavior of the Real-Time Group after 6 PM has been brought up.  We will talk more regarding this in our meeting next week.  It is important to note that we need to remain within the bounds of professional behavior at all times.  <NAME/> has a zero tolerance policy regarding harassment (language or behavior that offends or belittles others).

Thanks for your attention.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a244.xml">
  <body>

Thanks Robin !!  Have a great weekend.  I look forward to further business dealings.

Many thanks for all you help!!!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a245.xml">
  <body>

Cash till <NAME/> does a little better.   I'm swinging back to pizza now.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a246.xml">
  <body>

What's happening?  I understand you have a brand new truck.  Must be nice having money!!

I need 2 things from you.  

	1.	I found the title to the 4 wheeler and I was going to change it over to you name.  What do you think?  If that's ok, how do you want your name to show up on 		the title and what address should I use?

	2.	I'm getting ready to divy up the Dow stock.  How many of Dad's shares do you have?

Last thing, send me a million dollars, I'm tired of working.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a247.xml">
  <body>

When are we going to dinner?  Have you ever been to Paulies on Westheimer close to Shepherd?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a248.xml">
  <body>

How are you today?
The ball game last night was a disaster!
We give the "Bad News Bears" a bad name.
Example:  Runners on 1st and 2nd. I ask the third baseman what he will do if the ball comes to him.  He replies touch third base.  So the batter hits the ball down the third base line he runs up 5-10 feet from the third base picks up the ball and throws it to the pitcher.  I give up!  We lost 20 to 3

On a worse note.  Please don't say anything to anybody but <NAME/> just called and said Shannon has filled for divorce.
I hate to say this but he has created his own worse nightmare.  She has never earned a penny of the money she has become accustomed too, yet feels it should belong to her.  He has done nothing but foster this attitude.  Too bad its not legal to spank your spouse.
I will let you know what comes of things.

Why can't everything just work out instead of all this turmoil.  I hate all of this shit!  It hurts!

	Love <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a249.xml">
  <body>

Yes...sorry about implying that you did not have approval...
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a25.xml">
  <body>

Hello!

How are things going?  I'm pretty tired this morning, I went to get a relaxer last night and got there at 8p.m. and did not leave until 11:30p.m.--pretty exhausting, but <NAME/> is out of town today and I wanted to squeeze that in before he left and I'd have to get a sitter.  

Anyway, is everthing going well with the house?  <NAME/> so.....My daycare notified us yesterday morning when <NAME/> dropped the kids off that they will be closing their doors permanently on June 1st.  Talk about not getting much notice.  Anyway, needless to say, that is my new crusade!  

Talk with you later!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a250.xml">
  <body>

I think the industry needs to look at <NAME/> credit rating like a male looks at a women's Bra size.
A triple B is actually better than a triple A
What do you think?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a251.xml">
  <body>

There is a meeting scheduled for Wednesday, August 1, to reveiew how TW allocates
	through pools.  


	<NAME/> - Please see if you can possible get us 4102 and let us know where we will be meeting.

	<NAME/> - Please order food for 10 from Trebeards.  The combination red beans and rice and
	         shrimp et..... (don't know how to spell!!).  

	<NAME/> - <NAME/> is most interested in allocations through pools on the receipt side of the
		    business.  Doesn't mean she won't ask about delivery.  Let's discuss.

	
	Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a252.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>

Please RSVP no for me ( I will be out of town at a wedding).  Which reminds me.  We always need to send an email to <NAME/> (and <NAME/>? - ask <NAME/> for exact policy when I am out of the office for a day.   thanks
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a253.xml">
  <body>

The document below contains the guts of the tasking letter, I believe.  The GSA was in the other email.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a254.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, here is <NAME/>'s Mid Year review.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a255.xml">
  <body>

We are doing a gag gift exchange.  Usually it is pretty good, so try and bring something.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a256.xml">
  <body>

The only thing we need to make sure we are covered on is all the Huber purchases in the Powder <NAME/> will be starting on Dec 1.  They could be quite involved.  So let's make sure we are ready, especially if you are out.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a257.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, 

<NAME/> Olsen currently reports to me.  I fully recommend <NAME/> as a candidate for the Origination Track.  I don't think that he has decided which path he wants to take regarding his future, but I know that he would be very interested in discussing this track.  Please contact him at your convenience.  Thanks.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a258.xml">
  <body>

Please grant the following origination to Robin from TP1, deal #1162682.

thanks
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a259.xml">
  <body>

Please look at the attached redline from Greeley regarding the credit sections.  As you may recall a previous discussion regarding the exact name for the contract, the contract will be in the name of Atoms Energy Corp.  Please let me know asap.  Thanks
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a26.xml">
  <body>

Hi <NAME/>,

I just left you a voice mail.  I'm about to leave for the day but I wanted to let you know what I'm looking for.  I work on the East Desk at ENA and I'm trying to get copies of the following ENA and EES contracts.  These are the firm contracts listed on your ENA and EES notices dated November 29th and November 30th that I don't have.

ENA contracts
6020
5085
5072

EES contracts
6115
5916

I appreciate your help.  Please call me at 713-853-4743 of you have any comments or questions.

<NAME/> L. Germany
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a260.xml">
  <body>

Do you want to be on the call, if so can we use your office.

ds
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a261.xml">
  <body>

Good job of staying with this.  Thanks for all your help.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a262.xml">
  <body>

At the request of <NAME/> <NAME/>, I am forwarding for your
consideration a draft of a GISB between <NAME/> North America Corp. and
TECO Power Services.  Upon your review, please give me a call with your
questions and or comments.


	 
Regards,
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a263.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, we have looked at an automated way to take care of this issue.  So far we have not
	found an exceptable change.   It is a timing issue with true ups from the previous day
	which are not completed before the current day calcuations are done.  It is an item we 
	are manually monitoring today, but we are continuing to look for a better method.
	Thanks.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a264.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> and Deb, can you print colored copies of this chart for the Tuesday meeting?
	I wanted to go ahead and send this since it may take you awhile to print.  The rest
	of the presentation will be coming on Monday.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a265.xml">
  <body>

A third Master draft has been sent to <NAME/>.  I received confirmation, the draft has been sent to a contract analyst.  I have left a message, await their call.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a266.xml">
  <body>

http://salon.com/politics/feature/2002/02/08/enron_list/index.html
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a267.xml">
  <body>

Hi guys

I just remembered that we talked about playing today (1030?) Can anybody make it?  If not, let's try to reschedule.  <NAME/> all is well and I'll talk to you soon.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a268.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Long time...no nothing.  How goes it?  Just wanted to drop you a line and see how the fam's doing.  <NAME/> all is well.  We really need to grab a drink after work sometime or a late afternoon coffee and catch-up on each other's respective endeavours.

Talk to you soon,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a269.xml">
  <body>

Where are you located?  I'll come by to get them after I go to the credit union.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a27.xml">
  <body>

Hi <NAME/>

In accordance with <NAME/>'s call to you, here are revised drafts of the Modification Agreement and LC for your review.  By copy of this email I am at the same time circulating the documents for review by others at <NAME/>. I apologize in advance for not sending a blackline (a glitch here prevented me from making final changes in blackline) - if you are unable to make a marked copy from your prior version, let me know and I will attempt Tuesday morning to send you one. Thanks again for your help in getting this finalized.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a270.xml">
  <body>

FYI.  Just to keep you both in thel oop on some Oneok issues.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a271.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I will not be able to walk, but put me down for $25.00 for you.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a272.xml">
  <body>

This is the outage for redrock tie-ins and volumes.

ds
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a273.xml">
  <body>

For all that have missed the floor meeting,   we have been downgraded to "junk" status,  ending our merger plans and crushing our stock price.
A likely scenario would have us declaring bankruptcy within a few days.     Payroll is said to be funded until the end of the month, at least.   
If bankruptcy is filed,  payroll should be covered.
Another very real option is that the trading floor could be parcelled and sold to an outside company.   There are discussion underway that deal with this possibility.

Currently,  we are not trading.    We need to continue to report to work and keep a log of Real Time prices.    Continue to update the Hourly Prices sheet for a record of prices.    We may need these prices as support for liquidated damages.

More counterparties will be defaulting and cutting schedules.     Please make note of such cuts and prepare to bill LD's.   We have prepared a cut log for this purpose.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a274.xml">
  <body>

I sent you the fax yesterday.  It really looks like all the contracts were terminated effecitve 12/31/2001 to me.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a275.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

The flights sound great timing-wise and I know exactly where that hotel is located...being within walking distance of Pike's Market is always a bonus.  I look forward to the visit as well as the opportunity to finally meet everyone I've spoken with in person.

Thanks again,
<NAME/> <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a276.xml">
  <body>

The name sounds familiar but I don't know this guy.  He's over scheduling at El Paso.

<NAME/> Stickline  713-420-6463.  Good luck and let me know how it turns out.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a277.xml">
  <body>

Ranelle, <NAME/> and <NAME/>,  thought I would send this statement to you and see if this
	helps simplify our answer to your question.  

	The question is:  How is MDQ used in the nomination system to ensure we do not
	double up on MDQ volumes when we have split paths (i.e. nom on same contract
	from (1) Mid 15 to Bushton Inlet and from (2) Bushton Outlet to Demac)

	For Nominating purposes:

	MDQ of contract = Primary Firm + Alternate Firm up to the MDQ. 
	Anything over the MDQ will be Overrun and charged at the IT rate.

	Point MDQ needs to be considered when allocating a receipt point.

	EXAMPLE:

	If the Field MDQ is 10,000, then we will  (1) total the reciepts nominated on the
	contract; (2) compare the total nominated to the Contract MDQ.  Then the shipper
	will get firm (primary and alternate) up to their contract MDQ.  Anything over will be 
	overrun at IT rate.

	If anyone has any other questions, please let me know.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a278.xml">
  <body>

Actually <NAME/>, I will not be able to attend on the 5th.
Is there an alternate date?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a279.xml">
  <body>

Stewie,
How is it going with baby Wolf?   I want to make sure everything is ok before I call him.        Done any good deals lately?
At least tell me about hiking.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a28.xml">
  <body>

For the 6th, I borrowed 19,903 dth from EGHP (deal 1158684) and I must pay the all the gas back by Friday (deal 1158685).  Since we are borrowing the gas first, we should path this gas on contract # EGHP IT Loaning - 001.

Please let me know if you have any questions.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a280.xml">
  <body>

Good morning,

Yesterday for HE 10 and HE 11 we were cut Real Time by El Paso Electric on an import (EPMI_CISO_BLUE).  The import was cut by 30 mws and 42 mws respectively.  A purchase from the imbalance has been made.  Also for HE 12,  we bought back most of Harbor Cogeneration's schedule.  Harbor was going to run for 20 mws but could not.  We told Harbor that we would take the charge for them.  Therefore, the -20 mws of generation deviation for Harbor needs to be allocated to ECTRT as Load Deviation.  We put in a purchase of 20 mws from the imbalance in Enpower. 

Finally there is a variance for HE 17 and HE 18 possibly because of load shift from NP to SP.  We are flat in CAPS position manager.  And flat in Enpower.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a281.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

I just wanted to write and thank you again for affording me the opportunity to visit with you and all the other members of the  Puget trading team.  It was unfortunate we were unable to meet again before my departure so that I could have expressed the above in person, but email will have to suffice.  I very much enjoyed meeting with <NAME/>, <NAME/>, Dana and yourself, as well as with the other members of the gas and power staff.  You have a unique operation and one which appears to have many untapped opportunities that will undoubtedly make your time with the company fairly interesting for the foreseeable future.  I wish you the best of luck in your endeavors and look forward to speaking with you again in the future.

I went ahead and mailed all of my travel information, including receipts, to Jaquelyn <NAME/> as see was mentioned as the travel contact in one of your previous emails.  If there are any other measures I need to take on that front please let me know.

My previous difficulties with my other email service have been resolved.  Therefore, all of my future contact will most likely be through that email address.  In light of this, I simply ask that you direct any future email correspondence to: 

susan_m_scott@hotmail.com 

Once again thank you,
<NAME/> <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a282.xml">
  <body>

Sorry I'm already committed to another meeting.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a283.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, sounds good to me.  Iike that better than a formal presentation.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a284.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Could you do me a huge favor and have <NAME/> give <NAME/> <NAME/> of our credit department a call.  <NAME/> is having trouble getting through the pohone lines to you guys for some reason.  <NAME/> has tried to track down some financial information internally and has had no luck and doesn't know where else to look.  His number is 713-345-3923.  I really do appreicate you passing this message along.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a285.xml">
  <body>

Please see the attached.    Remember that we are planning on buying hour ending 7 (50 mw's).    So,   we wont actually generate 250's as the schedule indicates.
Alex will take care of this tonight.

Prices for the weekend look like:
onpeak $20.75
offpeak $ 12.25
gas  $2.06
This doesnt look too good for the weekend run.    Let me know what you need to do.


Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a286.xml">
  <body>

Lou, Gas Logistics (<NAME/> Corman's Group) performs the following services. 
	Where do these fall in your list of services in the Service Agreement? 
		Transportation Contract Services
		Nomination, Confirmation and Scheduling Services
		Gas Accounting (Billing of Transport)
		Commercial Support of Systems (working with the IT group)
		Gas Control (this was included in your list)
	If you have any questions, please give me a call.  Thanks. <NAME/> (Ext. 3-7637)
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a287.xml">
  <body>

Thanks you so much for working on these as fast as you have - there was a priority in getting them out.  However, as you know, the less cash outlay that we have right now the better.  Lets wait and try to offset the amount we owe them with what they owe us - so I say wait until you get July and August done.  What do you think the time frame is on this?  And when would be the earliest that we would make the payment?

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a288.xml">
  <body>

Hey,

The trip to Nashville was good...<NAME/> and <NAME/> actually live in Clarksville (which is about 45 mins NW of Nashville).  We went out to dinner in Nashville both Friday and Saturday night, and spent the day walking around downtown on Saturday.  <NAME/> drove me around the Army base and showed me a bit of the area where they live.  We also went to this Botanical Garden/Museum called Cheekwood...it's the estate of the <NAME/> Coffee fortune.  Anyway, it was fun and very relaxing.  They're house is really cute and their neighborhood requires at least a 1/3 an acre for each house...so there's lots of land.

I haven't made a decision about the Seattle job yet, I actually have until the end of next week to give them my answer.  In the meantime I've been talking to some headhunters and checking out any other options that may be out there.  At this point there is really no telling where in the U.S. I'm ultimately going to end up...which I personally find kind of fun.

We got a total of $350 out of the $400 deposit back (not too bad).  I just deposited the check so all I need to do is drop off a check for $175 to your Mom...which I will do this weekend.

<NAME/> things are still going well there!

Keep me posted,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a289.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, we will see if there is enough interest in doing a make-up session, we will certainly
	be glad to.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a29.xml">
  <body>

The Resolution desk has given me the password.   However,  <NAME/> was not set up in deal blotter under North America,  East Region.   I have since submitted another E-request for <NAME/>.   The reason is,   he cannot log onto blotter or create deals under his name.
Can you watch out for this?

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a290.xml">
  <body>

The following is a summary of the estimated costs of our buildout/subdivide project:

Blueprints	$6,000
Construction	$70,000
Furniture	$3,000
Voice/Data	$4,000 	
*Commisions	$16,000

*Commisions were negotiated by <NAME/> Realty

We had a profit of roughly $70,000 on the sublease over the term of the lease and will save approximately $11,000 per month on the sublease.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a291.xml">
  <body>

I predict that we will not prevail in an objection to consolidation. Judges love to consolidate unless there is a compelling reason not to do so. A one month delay will not be enough to persuade the AJL to not consolidate if you consider the advantages to the judges, so we would need a better reason.  Do we have anything else to go on?  (I don't think the Margate issue is enough, either.)

I doubt we will have the settlement buttoned up by the second week of December, which could leave us in the position of needing to continue the hearing until January anyway.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a292.xml">
  <body>

FYI:  Trish <NAME/> is playing at the Mucky Duck tomorrow night....thought you might be interested.  Drop me a line.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a293.xml">
  <body>

Was this the last day Tall tood the gas?  I bet so.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a294.xml">
  <body>

WOW, that was higher than I thought.  That is not much different than mine and higher than other Directors in the office.  I am not blowing smoke, but given my experience, there is nothing that I can do at the immediate time.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a295.xml">
  <body>

This is my Reliant Energy schedule.  I send this to all the people you see below at least twice a week.  I'm only doing business with them at one point and they are making money off <NAME/>.  But he has agreed to give me a little operational flexibility over the weekends if I need it.  I send them a wire every Thursday, unless its like this week where prices ran up and I had to send it on Wednesday.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a296.xml">
  <body>

In September, ENA agreed to purchase capacity from New Power on Transco.  The total demand charge should have been $9,000.00 on contract 4.0159.  New Power released the capacity volumetrically and I didn't catch it.  The actual demand charge billed was $270,000.00.  New Power agreed to reimburse ENA for the difference of $261,000.00.

ENA will pay the pipeline the billed demand charge of $270,000.00 and bill New Power $261,000.00 on deal 1110019.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a297.xml">
  <body>

Antoher thing they brought up was locking in physical basis only.  How does this affect credit?

Thanks again,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a298.xml">
  <body>

We met with SoCal today to discuss the changes SoCal is making for
	November 1.  Here is a high level recap in relation to impacts on TW:

	1.  SoCal will NOT set the capacity at needles lower than 750 unless
	     they have operational problems. And they will maintain 750 for a gas 
	     day (during all cycles).  (Good news for TW)

	2.  SoCal may set a capacity higher than 750.  If they do, they will
	     maintain that capacity for a gas day (during all cycles), unless there
	     are specific operational problems. (Good news for TW)
	   
	4.  SoCal will have the option to call OFO's at the beginning of each cycle
	     for the gas day, which could cause a confirmation reduction.  Today they
	     only call an OFO before the gas day begins.   Starting Nov. 1, they can 
	     call an OFO anytime before a GISB cycle, including Intraday 1 and 
	     Intraday 2 which are cycles in the gas day. (This will be a major impact
	     to SoCal's customers)

	5.  SoCal says the "windowing" is gone.  But, they are still giving us a
	     capacity and TW will continue to do the allocation if nominations
	     exceed their capacity.

	6.  SoCal can still reduce the scheduled volumes after an allocation.  This
	     would be due to SoCal's market not burning their schedule.  At that
	     time SoCal will confirm down to the market burn.

	Overall, our process does not change. If you have any questions, please
	let me know.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a299.xml">
  <body>

Thanks for your e-mail.  I will make changes as noted.  However, I am confused with regards to your corrections to Exhibit "D" as the draft does not include Exhibit "D".

 <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a3.xml">
  <body>

I'll ask my woman her opinion about my rock hard stomach.  I'm sure she will agree after I tell her what to see.  I guess women can be sensitive.

<NAME/>'s fine - and you?  How's your man?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a30.xml">
  <body>

i have notified Presto that I will be looking internally.    i am talking to portland,   as they want me back.      i have been moved to the Texas region to supply the Texas Choice and EES customers on an hourly basis.     I would manage this desk and, once again ,   have an hourly crew,  much the same as I did in California.      That is not the job I signed up for when I moved 3,000 miles to <NAME/>.      I have already been there,  done that and I am not  pleased about it so far,   but it will be allright.      If I did this job,   it would become a big success and then I would have to hear about how lucky I was.

I'll keep you posted......it's shit like this that keeps work interesting.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a300.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, thanks for the info.  Also should <NAME/> Dushinske be invited to this meeting?  He is the
Vice President over the North End Generation load and new services.  Just a thought.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a301.xml">
  <body>

here is a spreadsheet that captures the eol price data, an analyst here built it, apparently whenever the price changes in eol it gets sent to a file server and then the macro picks up the new data
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a302.xml">
  <body>

Hey,  just heard from the girls that you are now a tv star.  They saw you on some E! Entertainment special.  I am sorry to say that I missed it!  How are you and where are you?  I am assuming that you have now left the boat and are wondering your way to Austrailia.  <NAME/> you are enjoying yourself.  I just spent the weekend in Memphis - visiting family and friends.  It was a lot of fun!

If the show runs again and I am able to see it, perhaps I will record it for you!  Have fun and keep in touch!

K2
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a303.xml">
  <body>

Guys,

We are short for HE 21 through HE 23 at Malin. We are short at $40. The sale is to Pacificorp Power Marketing. 20 mws of the 50 is going to SMUD and 30 mws of the 50 is going to CERS. You can reference tag#'s 31892 and 31889.
If you have any questions just give me a call on my cell phone.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a304.xml">
  <body>

Early this afternoon would be fine, say around 1:30 PM.  My new location is 06456.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a305.xml">
  <body>

Hi <NAME/>,

I'm back in the office, and am working on this deal again.  Seems like there are a couple of items which need to be obtained so we can go forward expeditiously. Specifically, we need copies of the following documents:

	Lease agreement between CES and UST.

	Nortel RTU terms.

	Bankruptcy order allowing the sale of the switch from TCP to CES. 

I can speak with US Telenet's attorney regarding these requests, if you can get his/her name and number or email address.

I know there are some other issues, but getting these documents will really help.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a306.xml">
  <body>

This is for the other <NAME/> <NAME/>....I sit on 32.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a307.xml">
  <body>

Dale, how are we coming on this project in relation to the info <NAME/> sent you?
	Do you need anything else from <NAME/>?  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a308.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I believe you were out of the office on commodity close.  Who was reviewing
	the stack of reports on your desk?  Did we properly have the bases covered with
	you out?  Just trying to be sure we have the right coverage for accounting closes.

	Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a309.xml">
  <body>

Dari, looks good to me.  <NAME/>, do you have any comments?  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a31.xml">
  <body>

To my knowledge we are not building a power plant in Ontario.  I have been meaning to give you a call.  I will try sometime this week.

Talk to you later
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a310.xml">
  <body>

I have been wondering all week whether you got on the boat.  I looked at continental's specials and their weren't any for this weekend.  But if you plan ahead or are flexible on flight times, you can definitely get here for less than $200!

HOw was the rest of your trip?  Anything exciting to report?  How was your time with Turbo?  

I wish it were last wednesday!  I think I am going to sell all of my belongings and live on a beach somewhere!!

Let me know what's going on!

K2

oh Yeah,  I got some pictures back and will send you some.  what is your address?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a311.xml">
  <body>

Val,

What is this e-mail about, did you mean to send it to me?  Send me some of those funny jokes that are going around.


Talk to ya later!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a312.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

I need information regarding our monthly cell phone costs. I would like to cap per employee costs at $50 per month on the group calling plan. Effective in October, I would like employees billed for any amount they have over $50 per month on their cell phone. If an employee needs more minutes I would like to structure a plan to allow them to purchase more minutes through us--with them paying the extra per month.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a313.xml">
  <body>

I need your expertise.  If ENA nominated this gas, and I think we did based on what I see in Unify, then we are supposed to pay for it.  So I just need to verify with you  we TOOK this gas by nominating it.

Deal 1143983 on Natural Gas Pipeline Company.

thanks
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a314.xml">
  <body>

We understood,  at the time,   that the test was going well.     This is Frontera's test to continue to bid in replacement and non-spin.
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a315.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Attached are confirms for September and October.  Please let me know if you have any questions.

thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a316.xml">
  <body>

Is <NAME/> in default under the Sandhill agreements?  How about any other deals you know about, including the Mexico stuff?  Have you inherited Peoples (enovate) yet?  I suspect there may be a default there.  

I'm helping gather some of this info, and your help would be appreciated.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a317.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>
Looks like there is alot of work needed on <NAME/>'s draft. I'm working this weekend and hopefully we all can meet on Monday.  Meanwhile can you get from <NAME/> anything in writing that we used in connection with opposing the Bingham bill.  Those arguments would be very helpful to maybe repeat in the FERC response
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a318.xml">
  <body>

I've never run that file since it was split out, but my guess is you need to add any prior month adjustments and broker fees to today's file.  Tomorrow you will want to roll the file over to the new month...<NAME/> should be able to help you with that.  Make sure you also follow the Liquidation instructions for the gas daily post-id's...you can find them on that color coded sheet <NAME/> has.

Swing by if you need anything else.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a319.xml">
  <body>

Hi guys,

Just wanted to let you know that Palo Alto received some confirmations for transactions that they should not have received.  I think both are related to their term third party purchases that were entered into the system.  One was for 1500, which I think is related to their purchase from BP and one was for 1135 which are third party purchases from us and should already be in the system as several sale transactions to them.  I can fax copies of these confirms if anyone is interested.  Let me know if you have any questions.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a32.xml">
  <body>

This is what happened last time  when I tried to to send it.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a320.xml">
  <body>

Could you have someone draft an interruptible purchase agreement for Pioneer Oil.  I will forward you the address.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a321.xml">
  <body>

Ok...The flight option I've selected on Continental arrives at 5:17 pm Thursday and departs at 12:58 on Monday.  I haven't actually purchased the ticket yet, so if you want to get back to me to suggest anything else for some reason please don't hesitate.  However, if I haven't heard from you in the next hour or so I'll probably assume that the times are okay and just go ahead with the purchase.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a322.xml">
  <body>

to this spreadsheet we should add the $64MM cost for increased operating reserves, the $60MM for taxes and fx
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a323.xml">
  <body>

They are talking termination, which may not be justified for the asset management deal. <NAME/>'t know whether that would be a good thing or not.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a324.xml">
  <body>

Epcor Merchant & Capital LLP (formerly Encore)

Contract Contact:	<NAME/> Mikkelborg	phone: (403) 717-8121
Business Contact:	<NAME/> Laishley		phone: (403) 717-4610
						fax: (403) 7174601


<NAME/>

Business Contact:	<NAME/> Mah		phone: (403) 514-2078
						fax: (403) 514-3024
Credit Contact:		<NAME/> O'<NAME/>		phone: (403) 514-2073


TransCanada 

Business Contact:	<NAME/> Wenstrom	phone: (403) 216-2910
						fax: (403) 920-2464
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a325.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
	This is from a guy on our floor.  He's a summer intern...and this is his Tuesday morning story.  Incidentally I was standing directly in front of the old women picking out some green onions for my omelet when all hell broke loose.  I took about three steps back and wandered towards the kitchen in search of a fire extinguisher.  Didn't find one, and like <NAME/> (the intern) was a bit disappointed in my reactions...ah well.



I don't usually send out a group email, but listen to this shit.  So I am sitting at work this morning minding my own business when all hell breaks loose.  It is about 630am, and most of the trading has subsided for the morning.  I decide to grab the first ham and cheese omelet from the women that are serving our breakfast this morning because who knows how long the food will last...today is a special day because we get a fresh cooked breakfast from a propane grill as opposed to the green eggs and ham that we are used to because no one wants to get up at 3am and cook a fresh breakfast for <NAME/> employees, they usually cook it the night before. So, everyone on the floor is very excited and pumped up about the possibility of grabbing a nice breakfast without having the fear that later in the afternoon your ass would wreak havoc on you for eating the nasty green eggs.  So, I grab the first omelet and the crowd surges toward the two 70 year-old women at the grill.  Everyone is smiling, deciding whether or not they want ham or maybe they will get crazy and add salsa or something.  The next thing you know, straight out of a FOX tv show or "You've Gotta See This" episode...this old woman is engulfed in flames like the great fire of Chicago.  The propane tanks heating the stove exploded and the flames are high and wide, raising up to ten feet in height.  The place turns into a frenzy. Nobody can move, react, or anything.  Everyone is frozen watching this old woman(picture happy Gilmore's grandma) go up like an old Christmas tree.  A few seconds before this high school chemistry experiment, I was sitting on the first row right in the middle and I was staring at my two liquid display computer terminals and glancing at the sports ticker on ESPN2 on the 50inch Liquid FlatScreen TV that is directly above my desk. The old woman that went into flames is directly in front of me, about a literal three feet away and I am directly facing the inferno along with a co-worker who is catching the blunt of the heat of the flames. I don't save the old woman like most of you might have thought, I can't do anything but shout obscenities and wonder who the hell is going to jump in there and save this poor lady.  The old woman is yelling ,"Somebody get me outta here!"...yet we all continue to stare.....finally, someone grabs her arm and yanks her out of the blaze.  Who is this masked man, I have no clue.  However, I do witness <NAME/> from middle marketing doing his best <NAME/> Greene directly for the fire extinguisher of which he is the only one in the office that has a clue where it is. I see someone throwing a pitcher of egg yolk on the fire earlier, which is funny, if not for the fact that an old lady is missing half of her hair and her arms are about to blister up.  The blaze is extinguished after taking a hell of a toll on the old woman, ruining the flat screen tv that used to sit above me, and torching a bunch of cabinets and the backs of computer screens.  The alarm in our building 3 World Trade Center is screaming, and the smoke is enough to make even Polarek leave the area.  So, the fire departemnt comes and the old woman is now out of the building and on her way to the hospital.  Who knows what condition she is in, but all I know is I hope I am never around a bunch of vaginas(myself and the rest of us that did nothing) when I go up in flames someday.  Well, I have to get back to work because I have wasted about 20 minutes writing this drama.  Take care, <NAME/>


	<NAME/> you liked the show last night.
	Take it easy. B
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a326.xml">
  <body>

These are the mid values for the following deals.


Deal		Book			Mid Value
1065846	TP3 selling to TP1	NX1 + .13

1065497	TCO selling to TP3	NX1 + .08

241639		TCO purch from AEc	NX1 + .08
219618		TCO sell to AEC	NX1 + .08


Kimat, would you enter deal 1065846 and 1065497 in Tagg please?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a327.xml">
  <body>

Hey woman!!  How are things going?  Happy with the job?  Happy with the man?

Be carefull, something happened to my woman and she has a really big stomach.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a328.xml">
  <body>

Robin is having back surgery next Thursday, Feb 28th.  She went to a neurosurgeon for a second opinion, Dr. <NAME/> Aldama was her second opinion dude..  Dr. Esses, my second opinion dude, is an orthopedic surgeon.  And Dr.Alani, the guy I went to see first was an orthopedic surgeon.

Robin said I should go to a neurosurgeon.  What do you think?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a329.xml">
  <body>

Plan on a couple of hours.  I am not sure about lunch.  I may already have plans.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a33.xml">
  <body>

that's exactly the sense of pride in ourselves and our country we need to be displaying right now....go for it!!!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a330.xml">
  <body>

Thanks anyway...I eventually tracked it down yesterday.  

And yes, the real world emphatically sucks.  <NAME/>'s got the right idea, avoid it at all costs.  Still, work's going all right for me.  My hours have dramatically improved, which is nice, and they actually let me take time off for vacation.  I'm reserving the weekend <NAME/> mentioned in September so hopefully I'll see you there.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a331.xml">
  <body>

Lee <NAME/>, sounds like <NAME/> is our key person.  <NAME/>'t worry about it my request.

thanks
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a332.xml">
  <body>

Im doing great.  Its nice not having to work on Friday.
Weather is humid and cloudy.  It is suppoded to be hot this weekend.  Mid 80's most days.
I looked up the weather for Las Vegas also.  It should be perfect.
I hope the Aladdin has a nice pool area.  Think I will try and set up a massage for sometime Saturday.
We should try and run sometime Saturday?

I think <NAME/>, <NAME/> and I are on the same flight.
	Continental flight 1941  leaves <NAME/> 3:40 Pm arrives las Vegas 4:54 PM.
If you do not want to wait I will meet you at the Hotel.  Carry your cell phone and I will call or you can call me!
	return flight 1930 leaves Las Vegas 11:43 AM  arrives <NAME/> 4:49 PM

AC/DC isn't that a sexual conotation??????????????????????????????????
And why would that make your ears ring?  Im confused.

Be good and can't wait to see you on Friday!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!

	<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a333.xml">
  <body>

I have added Socal to the worksheet.  The prices listed are as of last night.  Nymex is up $.04 - $.05.  Basis is pretty much the same.  Let me know if you need anything else and I will let you guys know as soon as I get the option information.

thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a334.xml">
  <body>

These are pictures of the underground tunnel system.

ds
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a335.xml">
  <body>

I left a message regarding the GTC sent yesterday for this customer.  As we have a signed Master now from them, please reconfirm under this Master.  I have sent the Agreement to <NAME/> Richardson for handling.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a336.xml">
  <body>

I sent your request to Maire Heard in the Financial Group as we do not prepare ISDAs.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a337.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> and <NAME/>, as of today, we have emailed a list by station (7 and/or 16 day charts) to the measurement
	group which needs to be read for PPA's to correct the daily volumes fro the following shippers:

		MidAmerican - 147 stations (It is my understanding you have already 44 of the 147)
		IES - 87 stations
		Interstate Power - 6 stations
		Wisconsin Power and Light - 11 stations

	In order for Gas Logistics to keep track of the ones that need to be corrected, we would like for Measurement to send 
	us updates on the following information ASAP:

		1.  Which station numbers have or have not been corrected for October.

		2.  How many October charts have been received and how many are outstanding

		3.  Provide status of November chart information.

	Gas Logistics needs the October corrections in the system by December 19th, which is the time
	frame for the first prior period run.  This is important for us to be able to review the prior period invoices.
	As you 	find there are missing charts, if we can be of assistance in calling the field, please let us know. 
	This way, the measurement group can concentrate on reading the charts.

	We appreciate your assistance and help in tracking these prior periods and helping each of us to keep focused
	to get these prior period corrections done by the next months billing.  If you have any questions, please let
	<NAME/> or I know.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a338.xml">
  <body>

hey mojo...

sry about the missed call last night...had put my cell on silent mode for dinner and forgot to take it off.  hope you had a good night.  i really want to talk to you about the last week or so, sounds as if was an eventful one for both of us.  i'm really curious to hear how your appointment went today so drop me a line if you get a chance today and we can set up a firm time to have a rap session.

hasta,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a339.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>:  Please respond to <NAME/>'s question on when the Ad Val Tax is paid.  Please "cc" me on your answer also.

	Thanks,  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a34.xml">
  <body>

Group,

We have 25 mws of length in the BOM book at $56 again for 06/14/01 on peak.  This energy is in NP-15.  Please make deals under ST-WBOM.

ST-CALI has another 5 mws each hour on peak in NP-15.  See CAPS for other information.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a340.xml">
  <body>

Attached are additional drafts of agreements required in connection with the proposed Second Amendment to Master Netting Agreement, a draft of which I forwarded to you earlier. Please excuse the inconsistent reference to Sections - we are still trying to clean that up.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a341.xml">
  <body>

Send me your phone list as soon as you get a chance - my fax is 713-464-2391, phone 30685.
THanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a342.xml">
  <body>

Thanks for the information <NAME/>.  This looks good and useful.
Would you have any information on what tools we used to settle?  Or was it all a manual process?

B
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a343.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Our primary delivery point on the EP capacity is the border so it would have to flow as an alternative delivery location and would be subject to cuts.  I would like to talk to you in more detail about this with the assistance of <NAME/> Miller who is the tport expert in our group.  Then you can decide how you would like to persue.  <NAME/> will be available in the morning before 11:00 am CDT.

Please give me a call when you can -

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a344.xml">
  <body>

The physical basis offer indication for Dec - March at the City Gate is about $.32.  The fixed price indiation for the 38 month period you mentioned is approximately $4.39.    We need to discuss this structure in detail if you are serious about buying physical gas from us and we also need to get contracts in place. 
Let me know if there is anything else you need.

thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a345.xml">
  <body>

Until further,  it is best to avoid long positions in the morning hours that are to liquidate against the balancing market.    The downside is $1000 and the upside maybe $10.


Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a346.xml">
  <body>

Following are the contract terms for Iroquois and Tennessee.  I am more interested in getting numbers on Iroq contract 1250-05.  I believe we should not consider releasing the capacity for any term less than a year.


Pipeline			Iroquois
ENA Contract		125005
Rate Schedule		RTS12
MDQ			2,017
Receipt Point		Waddington
Delivery Point		South Commack
Beginning Term		3/1/2002
Ending Term		10/31/2006


Pipeline			Iroquois
ENA Contract		125008
Rate Schedule		RTS1
MDQ			35,465
Receipt Point		Waddington
Delivery Point		Tennessee Wright
Beginning Term		3/1/2002
Ending Term		3/31/2007


Pipeline			Tennessee
ENA Contract		29667
Rate Schedule		Net 284
MDQ			35,000
Receipt Point		Wright #012181  -      35,000 MDQ
Delivery Point		<NAME/> #020110  -        1,000 MDQ
Delivery Point		Leominster #020111  -  1,000 MDQ
Delivery Point		Revere #020116  -      11,200 MDQ
Delivery Point		<NAME/> #020191  -     1,800 MDQ
Delivery Point		Mendon #020285  -    20,000 MDQ
Beginning Term		3/1/2002
Ending Term		3/31/2001
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a347.xml">
  <body>

CALP released their 40,000 dth to ENA for Nov-01 through Mar-02.  The new contract number is 71451 and it should be set up in Sitara.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a348.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
I think you have the wrong <NAME/> <NAME/> as I do not work in <NAME/> or know Erin Copeland.
Please remove me from your distribution list.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a349.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> will give you minor changes.  Pleas make the changes and forward to <NAME/> <NAME/> with copies to <NAME/>, <NAME/> and me.  Thanks! - Teb
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a35.xml">
  <body>

Do these counterparties look familiar?  Call me when you get this please?

Thanks.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a350.xml">
  <body>

I just sent this to goodell so i wanted you to see what i got for Immer.

got a basket with a bunny in it, a big butterfly looking thing, a snickers bar, 2 caramel eggs, a baby binky, a mini mm candy dude - green, a double phone jack.  and seperately, a tiger (pooh) hand puppet.  phone jack is for me but im putting it in the basket.


so im gonna put her pedicure gift certificate at urban retreat in the easter basket.  i also got a happy b-day mylar baloon.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a351.xml">
  <body>

Here is the original email from Keoni, and the follow-up from <NAME/> <NAME/>.
Just give me a call with any questions.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a352.xml">
  <body>

http://www.co.montgomery.tx.us/webwiz/wwiz.asp?wwizmstr=WEB.CRT.STATEMENT&V1=00.9715.23.04800
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a353.xml">
  <body>

TJ,
Could you tell me what my balance is for vacation days?   Also,  I dont think that I have signed up for the floating holiday yet.   Would this balance reflect that?

Thank you!
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a354.xml">
  <body>

Fines:

     I know you have talked with <NAME/> but I wanted to give my two cents.  I think the fines are a great idea. We must be accountable for VAR.  However the fines do not allow the desks to push the envelope.  The desks need to stay a couple million under VAR to protect against volatility and factor changes.  We do not have the tools to predict our VAR with any strong degree of accuracy but we are penalized for going over a few hundred thousand dollars.  I propose a one day grace period of 10% to 12% over limit.  This would allow the desks to max their VAR and protect against unexpected changes.

EOL:

We continue to have trouble with brokers not working our EOL numbers.

We believe Dynegy has written a program to mirror our cash markets on their system. When we suspend, they suspend and as our markets move, so do theirs.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a355.xml">
  <body>

NOW THAT's WHAT I LIKE TO HEAR!!!!

Thanks Drew.

Ok, no more bad talk about Drew for the rest of the week.  Is today Friday?



just kidding
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a356.xml">
  <body>

Ricki, no problem.  Let's also book 4194 for the day and I will talk to 
the three people that have meetings in 4194 to let them know they
could use my office.   Are you OK with that?  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a357.xml">
  <body>

I won't be available from2:00 to 2:45 mountain time
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a358.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, did you send out last weeks notes?  If so can you resend to
	team advisors and coordinators.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a359.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, on NNG and TW, things were quiet.  The SoCal/West of Thoreau spreadsheet
	is on your desk.  

	Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a36.xml">
  <body>

We have a very good relationship, and long term gas sale with Thermo Partners who manage the 270 MW Ft. Lupton facility.  They have inquired as to <NAME/>'s interest in either buying the energy, tolling or buying the entire plant.  The effective date would be July 2002.  The plant is currently under a QF contract with PSCo.

<NAME/>, I would like to see if you have some time on Monday afternoon to discuss the particulars and we can devise a game plan to get you connected with these guys.  Let me know your availability.

<NAME/>
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a360.xml">
  <body>

This is what we discussed with <NAME/> a few months ago.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a361.xml">
  <body>

What did you do in Rome????  you must have had Capt. <NAME/>.  I understand that he is a big golfer.  when did you go?  I can do lunch - what time?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a362.xml">
  <body>

Prepay amount for tomorrow is $30,000.00.  I gave <NAME/> the hard copy of the wire request.

Thanks team.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a363.xml">
  <body>

Tennessee requires a pepayment or LC in the amount of $25,000.00 per SA pool.  For the Keyspan deal, that essentially means we would need $25,000.00 of credit for each point, 500L, 800L, and Zone 0 = $75,000.00 total.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a364.xml">
  <body>

Thanks, you too.  How do I get my fax number changed in the contract?  My current fax number is 713-646-3037.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a365.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
I left a message for you today concerning your e-mail.      Do you still need someone?     I would like to ask you some specific questions again,  so give me a call.      I am at 3-7160.      

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a366.xml">
  <body>

I found a mistake in my capacity worksheet.

The term on the Boston Gas capacity, contract 125008, 35,465 MDQ, is 12/1/1998 - 3/31/2007.  I think have the ending date as 2008.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a367.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>....How was the weekend??????  Very curious to see what you crazy girls did up there in Whistler.  

So, I wanted to let you know that Puget called me last Friday with another job opening.  I'm supposed to talk to the guy today regarding the position.  I certainly don't want to get my hopes up...but I'm kind of excited about this being something I could actually like.  

<NAME/> all is well with you and I'll let you know how my phone call goes today.

Talk to you soon,
<NAME/>

Btw...messengered with <NAME/> yesterday, I guess things are back to "normal" - whatever that is.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a368.xml">
  <body>

I did the following deals with Ms Overton yesterday.

Rolled the park & loans to November.

Purchased 3 transport contracts - 500L to Broad Run.
1.  2500 day for Nov-Jan
2.  2500 day for Feb-Mar
3.  3893 day for Nov only.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a369.xml">
  <body>

These days, its easier for our legal department to draft or approve a new GISB than to find any of the existing documents.  The attached document is for <NAME/> North America Corp.  <NAME/> is going to see if they can use it.

If your legal department approves, please print 2 originals, fill in the Sempra information, sign it, and send it to me.

<NAME/>

                                                                            Address:	Attn:  <NAME/> Germany  ECS 04444
		1400 Smith St
		<NAME/>, TX 77002
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a37.xml">
  <body>

just to double check;  the meeting is now on Monday,  right?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a370.xml">
  <body>

Raetta, would you please work with <NAME/> and have him do the same process you have
	done with NNG.  Thanks for everyone's help.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a371.xml">
  <body>

Before you know it, we're gonna start outnumbering you guys.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a372.xml">
  <body>

Fellas,

Presto has asked me to be the contact to <NAME/> <NAME/> at PIRA with regard to setting up an arrangement for their consulting services.  I'm currently having information-gathering discussions over services and fees for both gas and power, in both the east and west.  In order to fully incorporate everyone's needs into our arrangement with PIRA, I'll be contacting you this week to gather requests.  Or, if you know what you need, please just reply to me with the specific information.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a373.xml">
  <body>

Transco/<NAME/> says the $700,000 they owe NNG has been processed and
	should be wired by Tuesday.  We will let you know if anything changes.

	Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a374.xml">
  <body>

Team, I would like for you to review the attached Shipper assignment list.  With <NAME/> leaving and
	<NAME/> still on a learning curve, I wanted to throw out some possibilities and get your input.  I did not
	spend a lot of time on interconnects, so you may want to look at those closely.  I did talk with <NAME/>,
	Terry, Raetta and <NAME/> for input.  Please review, discuss and set up some time to visit with me about
	your comments.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a375.xml">
  <body>

The latest from Frontera:
They will not run unless we receive an OOME.  Call me if you need to,  but call before 10pm.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a376.xml">
  <body>

For gas day 5/7/02, Cinergy/Apache moved 10,000 dth from Sid <NAME/> Cayanosa to Oasis Mi <NAME/>.  Oasis Mi <NAME/> is not a Lone Star point but I didn't know it at the time and I sold the gas to TXU at $3.20.  No sales were made for 5/8/02.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a377.xml">
  <body>

Stacy and I will be discussing changes to the Master Agreement on Friday.  Please send me an email and cc <NAME/>, and  Stacy,  requesting changes to Section 4.1,4.2  to delete "on a monthly basis" re the call for a letter of credit.

Dp
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a378.xml">
  <body>

Everyone on each desk is an EOL trader.  Please continue to include the East Desk on your daily lunch list.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a379.xml">
  <body>

Sell 75 Contracts May, 2001 NYMEX @$5.36
Buy 75 Contracts May, 2001 NYMEX @$5.28
Buy 100 Contracts May, 2001 NYMEX @$5.285
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a38.xml">
  <body>

Group,
When tiering adjustment bids, the CAISO system will not read more than 10 bids. Also, remember to have the tier monotically increasing.
Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a380.xml">
  <body>

In connection with Deloitte & Touche's annual audit of MGAG, Deloitte & Touche is trying to confirm what MGAG has billed ENA for the year ending December 31, 2001.  I would normally send this request directly to settlements.  However, it is my understanding that all request should be coordinated through you due to our circumstance.  

If I don't hear from you by 2:30 PM this afternoon, I will send you the 13 page fax I received from Deloitte & Touche and I will give them your name and number as the contact person to comply with their requests.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a381.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
Could you please sign up <NAME/> Meyers, <NAME/> Guzman, and <NAME/> Symes for the pilot program.
Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a382.xml">
  <body>

El Paso and Reliant don't have time to talk about right now but I'm also having a problem telling them about the deal because there are too many unknowns.  It's not the same as selling parked gas on Sonat.

Still working it though.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a383.xml">
  <body>

If I already sent this to you just ignore this!
I will need a new chair for the new building!
The one I have now does not cut it.
Please order one like I have now!

	Thanks, <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a384.xml">
  <body>

Hi <NAME/>,

I've been trying to get a hold of <NAME/> this morning, but am not certain if she is in the office today.  My current situation has become somewhat interesting over the last several days and I was hoping to be able to talk over some things with her.  If <NAME/> is in fact out of the office today would you mind if we talked at some point.  I'm under some deadlines around here and would be very grateful to have an opportunity to discuss things with <NAME/> or yourself.

Thank you,
<NAME/> <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a385.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, 

I have passed your resume on to <NAME/> and to <NAME/> Vickers, who is <NAME/>'s equivalent for the East and Central desks.  I hope you hear from one of them - <NAME/> is an awesome guy and I would work for him anywhere! I will keep you posted as I hear of other opportunies you might be interested in.  

I will do whatever I can to take care of Robbie <NAME/>! 

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a386.xml">
  <body>

Hey guys - it looks like NCPA got our proposal and would like for us to refresh by 9 am PPT tomarrow morning.  That is 11 our time.  <NAME/>, where are we with credit and contracts.  I think we need to have this done today.  Can you let me know what our status is?  <NAME/> is asking me.  <NAME/>, can we refresh in the morning fairly quickly?  I would love to get this deal done.  Tomarrow, we need to add a little orig!  Please let me know if any of you have any questions.

thanks, 

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a387.xml">
  <body>

Group,

When doing swaps please use the swap function in Enpower. Do not enter annuities anymore for financial deals. Be sure to specify whether you are buying or selling index and then what index you are selling (NP15 inc/dec...etc).  An example appears in the attachment.  Swaps have caused disputes that have dragged on for months in the past, so call me with any questions.  
Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a388.xml">
  <body>

TJ,

Please put the Central Desk Gas meeting on my calendar every day 2:30 - 3:00.  Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a389.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> attached is a draft of a Master Firm Purchase/Sale Agreement for Kaztex Energy Management.  Please give me a call if I can be of further assistance.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a39.xml">
  <body>

It's pretty scary!  Shows the state of the industry, doesn't it?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a390.xml">
  <body>

Ricki, it might be quicker to re-create the timeline.  I can give you a colored copy so you
can keep it identical to the one we have.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a391.xml">
  <body>

Kelley,

I am writing to you to follow up on our discussion last week regarding disclosure of counterparty names for price verification purposes.
Can you give me the name and contact information for the person within your company that would work with us to put a Confidentiality Agreement in place.
<NAME/> Hodge is our lawyer who will work on this for <NAME/>.  <NAME/> can contacted at 713 853-6911 or by email at jeffrey.t.hodge@enron.com. 

Thanks for you assistance.

<NAME/> <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a392.xml">
  <body>

I've tried to send this back to <NAME/> twice.  Would you please forward it to her?  She will be needing this list.

<NAME/>


 
I don't know if she has registered yet so I've come up with a few items that I think the baby will need.  Please share this humble list with the appropriate people.  I do work for a bankrupt company you know.

Item			Price
2002 Range Rover 	$64,896             http://www.edmunds.com/new/2002/landrover/rangerover/index.html
2002 Porsche Boxster	$50,000		http://www.edmunds.com/new/2002/porsche/boxster/index.html
<NAME/> Hatcher		$$$		http://www.eonline.com/Facts/People/Bio/0,128,19,00.html
Natilie Imbruglia		$$$$		http://www.eonline.com/Facts/People/Bio/0,128,67918,00.html
Toshiba Big Screen	$2,189		http://electronics.cnet.com/electronics/0-6342372-1304-7297512.html?tag=pdtl-list
Harley Davidson		$21,000		http://www.harley-davidson.com/motorcycles/motorcycles_detail.jsp?PRODUCT%3C%3Eprd_id=432813&FOLDER%3C%3Efolder_id=440145&bmUID=1015517216967
Blue Wave Boat		$18,000		http://striperguide.tripod.com/bluewave.htm
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a393.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
we often trade with EPMI, as they may be the best bid on any given day.      So,   the language should apply.

Thx,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a394.xml">
  <body>

Here is an opportunity to get a box for one of the games.  Detroit on Feb 4th would be great!  That is a Monday.  If you and <NAME/> wanted to you could come up and ski that weekend prior.  Let me know what you think.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a395.xml">
  <body>

Fine, I was thinking of you earlier today.  Just had a bite to eat and just sitting here surfing the net.  Looking for some good vacation spots.   just happened to be looking at Arizona for the heck of it.  

How is you day going so far?  Already had lunch?  How did the car shopping trip go on Saturday?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a396.xml">
  <body>

I will be out of the office next week on vacation.

Monday July 30    out
Tuesday                in
Wednesday          out
Thursday              out
Friday                  out

I will be packing and beginning to move into our new house if you have any questions
just page and I will get back with you or voice mail or E:mail.

Thanks DS
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a397.xml">
  <body>

Hey Jimbo,

Good morning,

<NAME/> you please send me your address and fax number, we're going to try and get some contracts sent our sometime real soon.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a398.xml">
  <body>

Dahlke,

I purchased a gas deal,   10,000 mmbtud - HSC for 7/10-7/31 for $3.15.   I bought this through <NAME/> G-S.
Wont you take the final prints for each day and calc profitability for me,  or how do you do this?

Please give me some money

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a399.xml">
  <body>

Dale, what is the timing for adding this information.  Also are you
	or <NAME/> setting up the meeting to discuss the accounting imbalance
	info?  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a4.xml">
  <body>

Carmen,
Please note that my employee's correct name is Alex McElreath.  It was mispelled below.

Thank you,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a40.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
I believe this was meant for <NAME/> <NAME/> in Technical Assets.
Please note the difference in email addresses.
Thanks, 
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a400.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, here is your draft for Noresco. Call me if you have any questions. I realize the name is wrong on the file I will change this, it is correct in the contract.

 dp
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a401.xml">
  <body>

We could meet at my house and sit on my patio.  I should stick around until 5:30 or so.  I could be home by 5:45 or 6.  Is that cool?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a402.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, we need to meet first thing Monday to see where you are on the Agenda for
	Tuesday's meeting plus I need this presentation in power point Mondy morning
	as well.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a403.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
Your cell phone is not working or has been disconnected and I have no way to reach you. Please update me with your contact information as soon as possible.
Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a404.xml">
  <body>

figured out what it is that grates on me w/ smith.....he is monumentally patronizing to me....and i REALLY don't like being talked down to or made to feel inferior....if i'm not on my guard, my reactions to this behavior run the risk of being swift and strong....
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a405.xml">
  <body>

This is an email sent to me after my conversation with <NAME/> last week.  I don't know where he is leading with this.  However will
every one please read the below and Jerry in my absense please work with everyone to try and come up with a solution that 
TW is willing to live with as we go forward as TW and EMAR (operators for Citizens).  
Sorry I won't be able to any help this week as I will be traveling to New Mexico for my Mom's funeral.  I will try and stay in the
loop as best I can.  Thanks for everyone's help in resolving this issue.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a406.xml">
  <body>

I'm forcasting $30,000.00 to be paid to Reliant this Friday for the Tallahassee deal.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a407.xml">
  <body>

FYI, I have started negotiations with LG&E, however they have not resolved the issue of party name(s) on their part.   I will keep you apprised of my progress.

dp
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a408.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> and Raetta, please work with Randy to ensure we get the anaylsis done
	and that we are all comfortable with the results.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a409.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I will be out of the office on Monday, Oct. 22nd., but <NAME/> and <NAME/> can work with
	<NAME/> and the team to meet on MOPS scheduling.  I would like for you to meet with
	<NAME/> and <NAME/> before the 22nd to be sure we are comfortable with what information to
	pass back and forth.  

	<NAME/>, would you take the lead working with <NAME/> and <NAME/> to cover the meeting on Monday.

	Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a41.xml">
  <body>

mbfleming3: yo
Trogg 522: <NAME/>
mbfleming3: hows the week going for you
Trogg 522: i'm so so tired
Trogg 522: i want to go to sleep in the worst way.
mbfleming3: take a day odd
mbfleming3: off
Trogg 522: no no no, i do like to take fridays off though
mbfleming3: fridays would be better
mbfleming3: so my job search is over.
Trogg 522: yes sir, i mite do that too. REALLY
Trogg 522: so whats the scoop
Trogg 522: you are going to work for barer rite
mbfleming3: going to work for marathon oil
Trogg 522: barker
Trogg 522: cool, where are they
Trogg 522: when do you start
Trogg 522: what are you going to be doing
Trogg 522: can i tell everyone
mbfleming3: one at a time
Trogg 522: oh don't worry, i wrote them all one at a time
mbfleming3: i meant one question at a time
mbfleming3: they are off of san felipe in the galleria
mbfleming3: i start next monday/tuesday
Trogg 522: how many people are you echattig with at this moment?  STOP IT and answer my questions
mbfleming3: i was on the phone
Trogg 522: oh, ok
mbfleming3: i will be starting a new group doing business develp and marketing 
Trogg 522: can i tell everyone?
Trogg 522: or do you want to do that.
mbfleming3: you can tell people
Trogg 522: so what is your tittttle
Trogg 522: New Group?   what business are you going to develope?
mbfleming3: phone call please hold
Trogg 522: grrrrrr
mbfleming3: still working on my title.  i will be marketing their existing assets and then any discoveries they have looking to find markets for it and also they are wanting to become more marketing oriented as opposed to just trading their existing supply
Trogg 522: WOW, you ARE the MAN.
mbfleming3: great group.  not very biga nd not very fat (very flat org chart)
Trogg 522: Well congradulations.  I'm sure I'll love having you as a new boss.
mbfleming3: what was your name again
Trogg 522: shoe shine and car wash boy
mbfleming3: well, that means that you will have to come out my way sometime so i can buy you some lunch
Trogg 522: <NAME/>'t you worry.  I'll be there.
Trogg 522: <NAME/> said she was very happy for you.
mbfleming3: thank you
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a410.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I see you didn't approve my access for AEP which is fine.  I only need access to all the Estate desks and I just asked <NAME/> to give me everything because I don't know where the deals are for the other desk.  I didn't know if the Central Desk deals are under Central Desk or one of their many other books.  I think I just need Central, East, West, and Texas.

But, maybe you can help.  My request for the Central Desk needs <NAME/> Giron's approval and he's not in the People Finder.  So he's either at UBS or he left the company.  Do you know who I should be approving that now?

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a411.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I'm faxing you official statements from the pipeline and I'm going to mail them to <NAME/> Vos.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a412.xml">
  <body>

Just a reminder that we still need to discuss the physical deals with volumes in the sitara for March.  You said we were going to talk to <NAME/> Hall about that today.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a413.xml">
  <body>

I need to get with <NAME/> Duff and have him add the new point to the map.  <NAME/> can you do this for us.
This new point will need to be inserted under the Mapco point on the <NAME/> to Blanco column.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a414.xml">
  <body>

Nosir.  You are the man working on this FREAKY pipe.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a415.xml">
  <body>

But Oregon would be eaten alive by Miami - they haven't played anyone this year.  Just got a call about a power originator job in <NAME/>.  Interesting!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a416.xml">
  <body>

No flying, my brother and I have a pontoon boat.  It has a potty on so I think it will work.  Next Wed it is.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a417.xml">
  <body>

Greetings:

For tonight,   Frontera is long 85mw's hour ending 2300.    We need to sell this under the Teco Services book.


For tomorrow Frontera needs to sell:

hour ending  4 - 30 mw's
hour ending 5 -30 mw's
Enter a purchase from Frontera (Teco services book) enter the same price as you sold for.
Enter the sale (Teco Services).

I am also selling Frontera 200 mw's for hour ending 7 and 50 mw's hour ending 8.
I am selling this position for $26.04.       I will be short the Imbalance price during this time. 
If you can buy below $26.04 for this time period,  do so and schedule to load  in the South.       

I am long into the North Zone as follows :
he 1-6,    40 mw's
he 23&24,   55mw's

I am long under deal #834600
If prices appear to weaken,  sell these mw's for 1-6 and cut this Ercot Imbalance deal by same.    This deals should be listed under Ercot Asset.


Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a418.xml">
  <body>

I called your work number and noooooo body anwsered!!!!!!!  We are going to lunch with <NAME/> today.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a419.xml">
  <body>

Are you sure you have the right <NAME/> <NAME/>?  If this is for Click at Home, I've already received my computer.  Try the <NAME/> <NAME/> with legal...her extension is 30596.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a42.xml">
  <body>

Please see the attached Master Spot Purchase/Sale Agreement for Pioneer Oil Company.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a420.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
apparently an imbalance deal was entered under Teco services and the mark to market flag was not removed.    I show negative new deal value for Teco Services,  when I sold above the curve on their behalf.
I assume this is the reason for the negative new deal value.

The deal has been revised,  as it was to be a temporary placeholder anyway.   This imbal. sale deal will be taken to zero and resold to another counterparty tonight.

<NAME/> I ever get a true up for the negative new deal value?

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a421.xml">
  <body>

you look very intense....what happened to the pwr meeting?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a422.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>'t forget about me.  I'm still trying to find out what it will take to move gas on and ENA tabs agreement.  No transportation at this point, just a tabs.  Also, it will be much easier for you guys to monitor because most of the deals will be monthly.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a423.xml">
  <body>

Thanks for the words - given my week, my month, my year, I need all the reminders I can to refocus and prioritize.  <NAME/> all is well with you.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a424.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

What's your suggestion?  We are looking at a PA in connection with Tennessee Pipeline's open season. (did I get that right?)
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a425.xml">
  <body>

So do we have a special agreement in place for the full requirements gas deal?  I think that you did that deal before I came to the gas desk.  How can I get a copy of the penalty language?

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a426.xml">
  <body>

What do I need to do to get approval to trade crude?  I'm officially bearish now...would be selling wildly short right here @ $27.50

fletch
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a427.xml">
  <body>

Robin Barbe followed up with a phone call.
 
I've told <NAME/> that this wouldn't be resolved until we resolve all of our Dominion issues.  AND I TELL HER THIS ABOUT ONCE A WEEK.  Please forward her to me in the future.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a428.xml">
  <body>

We cannot enter into  a contract with TXU as they require ENA to warrant gas sold is "intrastate" gas.  For obvious reasons this is not possible.  Please give me a call should you wish to discuss this further.

Dp
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a429.xml">
  <body>

What do you know about Panda Resources?  Nothing in a rush right now but I am showing them 10 year prices for their plant in AZ.  I would, however, like to be prepared to do bidness!  Let me know what you need.

Thanks,

Ki.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a43.xml">
  <body>

Hey!!!!!    Is the wedding still on for Sunday?

		IF YES, then, are we invited or do you want to keep it small?

			IF NO, then, hey I understand - I'm not sure what we are going to do either.  She doesn't like the Vega idea.
			IF YES, then, when and where?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a430.xml">
  <body>

Group,
Here is some input from <NAME/> at EPE regarding running their system. I think the EPE system was run very well on October 18th, but aside from that, this email shows how closely they are watching our performance and what they expect. Let's do our best to continue to provide them with good service.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a431.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, 

If you have a minute, will you look at this term sheet?  His volumes are really small but if we get the Palo Alto deal it won't be that big of a deal - unless we have to schedule less than 1 MMBtu. Oh yo!  His average daily volume, for both plants is about 178/day, based on annual usage.  I have proposed basically a GD deal with a first of the month index option if he can set a BDQ.

Thanks in advance.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a432.xml">
  <body>

I think this was intended for the other <NAME/> <NAME/>.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a433.xml">
  <body>

Probably tomorrow.  I got a feeling that <NAME/> would like to visit with you about it.

Dismal here.  How are you?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a434.xml">
  <body>

okay, i haven't made a check out yet if you still want to pay this one.  i can bring it home tonight....wow on the priya thing, that really stinks....
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a435.xml">
  <body>

"Big" performances I'd like to/be willing to see:

<NAME/> Chicks (2/12) 

<NAME/> Lovett and <NAME/> McBride (2/18)

Emmylou <NAME/>, <NAME/> Krauss, <NAME/> Loveless and Nickel Creek (2/23)

Willie <NAME/> and Lee <NAME/> Womack (2/26)

"Legends of Rodeo <NAME/> in Concert" (3/2)....really, how can we miss this one?

<NAME/> Straight (3/3)

Lesser knowns/has beens at other venues:

Statler Brothers (1/17,1/18)   -  Galveston Oprea House

<NAME/> <NAME/> (2/2)   -  Arena Theatre
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a436.xml">
  <body>

Jerry, <NAME/>, <NAME/> and <NAME/>, we can meet in my office to dial into the conference call
	if you like.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a437.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> the GISB is not attached to this email. Please resend.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a438.xml">
  <body>

On September 24, 2001, <NAME/> gave each of you a list of your outstanding accounts receivable
	back to January, 1998.  In meeting with <NAME/> today, I understand, we have NOT cleaned up very
	many of these issues.
	
	<NAME/> will be getting with each one of you AGAIN to review your accounts.  My expectation is
	that there has been some clean up activity before Performance Reviews at which time I will
	ask <NAME/> for an update.  <NAME/>, Raetta and <NAME/> are all available as needed to help you in
	this effort.

	All clean up should be completed by December 31, 2001.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a439.xml">
  <body>

Here's what I got from <NAME/> on the lease.  The numbers don't seem to match, but we won't worry about that now.

The Nortel RTU info is supposed to be here by Wednesday. 

<NAME/>, please make the few changes to the draft equipment lease <NAME/> previously prepared to incorporate the new terms.  To the extent necessary, just bracket any questions you have, especially commercial questions.  We won't tackle the security agreement or the license agreement yet. Just send the revised lease to me (not <NAME/> yet).

Please see if you can find the bankruptcy proceeding.  If the docs aren't available on line, please get back to me before incurring any additional expense.  I don't want to spend a lot of money on this until things become a bit more clear.  

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a44.xml">
  <body>

Linus,
can you give me the info for a New Power contact?

jmf
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a440.xml">
  <body>

We need a written letter from the previous agent regarding transfer to new agent as well as a written document from the new agent consenting to same.  In addition,  the contract party should consent and acknowledge this transfer in written form.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a441.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

$4.87 is the correct price for this deal. Waha did not trade above 4.94 on 3/23.  This is an EOL deal, so Conoco should be able to easily check their records to confirm this.

D
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a442.xml">
  <body>

Sure,  I am online everyday.
I get in about 6 am, usually putting the numbers on at 6:30.   I start with hr ending 8-22 and change to 9-22 usually when the first interval of he 9 is printed. 
This is at my discretion.   
You may post a limit order (either a bid or offer) that covers mine and transact online.   You wont necessarily be trading with me,  another counterparty can lift your offer or hit your bid.

Let's trade it up!!!

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a443.xml">
  <body>

hey courtney,

i'm sorry i didn't reply back to you sooner, but i'm sure you'll understand when i say that things with work have been a bit on the crazy side.  i'd like to attend tonight, but have a bit of a scheduling conflict.  i was wondering if it would be alright if i showed up between 7:30-8:00 rather than at 7:00.  also, where exactly are the festivities going to be held?

thanks,
susan
713-853-1455
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a444.xml">
  <body>

Yonnie,

I hope you are doing well.  I just talked to Wende and we discussed having lunch with you on the 26th.  My flight isn't until 7 pm that day and I would love to see you.  I hope you will be able to make it!  My job search is going well.  I was in <NAME/> yesterday and that looks promising.  I may just wait for the new deal here to go through to see what is still left with the "new company".  I am traveling Jan 3 - 12 so it just makes sense to wait!

We can chat more when I see you!  Let either me or Wende know if you can make it!

Talk to you later -

Love,  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a445.xml">
  <body>

Here is an unproofed draft of examples.  Please forward to the appropriate people at LLG.  Thanks
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a446.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
On Tuesday we sold the CAISO replacement reserves at Malin for HE 15 and HE 16, then HE 18 through HE 22.  We were exercised for the first 40 minutes of HE 15 (for the last 20 minutes of HE 15 our energy was uninstructued and we received the dec price).  For HE 16, and HE 18-22 we were awarded the capacity payment but were not exercised.  The capacity payment should be at least $91.86 for each hour it was received.  If you have questions, please let me know.
Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a447.xml">
  <body>

I would prefer that you fix it.  Just come over when you are ready.

thanks
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a448.xml">
  <body>

Go to the first website shown below (http://www.enerfax.com).  Scroll down once you get to this website and you will see an article about fuel cells.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a449.xml">
  <body>

Was on a conference call with <NAME/> (TW gas control) and <NAME/> Gruel (Griffith plant) Monday morning (September 3) 
concerning pressure drop at the Griffith plant.  It was discovered that the TW mainline setpoint had been changed to 
reflect the new order of 35,000 for the day.  The plant sent TW a schedule of hourly burns for the day.  They had 
intended to take their 24hr rate with-in 12 to 14hrs.  Asked <NAME/> to raise the TW mainline setpoint to approximately 
120,000.  
After speaking with <NAME/> off line and asked him to open the spead sheet from <NAME/> on their takes asked him to figure
the hourly take for the 24 hrs.  He said that he made a mistake and didn't look at it.  The Griffith plant has been on line
since sometime in April and this should not be anything new to the gas controllers.
Asked <NAME/> to call <NAME/> back with Griffith and make sure they had Gas controls E:mail address and or fax number to send
any revisions. 

Thanks DS
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a45.xml">
  <body>

Early to my appt, so I'm working some.  Could you find <NAME/> Mims number at VE? We will also need his fax number.

Talk to you later.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a450.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Attached is a graph showing storage year by year.  We are expecting another rather large injection this week.  Cal 02 Nymex is up about $.0125 but the balance of 01 is down about a penny.  There is no weather to speak of and therefore,  no demand for physical gas - this is what is driving prices down.  Let me know if you have any questions.  Am still working on the option pricing.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a451.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
My address is <NAME/> <NAME/> III,
Please make the correction.
Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a452.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> I have sent <NAME/> <NAME/> with Texican a redline version (attached) regarding Threshold changes, to which he does not agree.  In addition, he is insisting language regarding LC's "On a Monthly basis" be retained.  Please talk to him regarding credit issues and let me know.  We did not discuss the MAC.  These are the only issues remaining.  Thanks for your help.

 

AGL Energy Services, LLC as you know has become Sequent Energy Management, L.P.  They are ready to sign our Master however,  I need your input concerning the credit worksheet sent 4/01.  Do you want to change this?  If not, I will proceed with final negotiations.  Thanks!!!!!!!!!!!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a453.xml">
  <body>

Please respond for me.  You should probably notify them that it will be changing with the sell of HPL.

	Thanks,   <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a454.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> 

Can you get <NAME/> and me a copy of the applicable contract/tariff.  Thanks
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a455.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, the way the accounting system works today:  Dec. 1 - 20 flow will be attributed  to the
	contract that nominated at that point for the 21 through 31.  This automaticall happens if there
	is no OBA at the point and if there is only one contract nominated at the point.  If we do not want
	that to happen, we need to discuss our options. Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a456.xml">
  <body>

Why are we doing a hot tap?  Is this a new I/C?   If so is it a receipt or delivery.  Seems like gas control doesn't know anything about it.

Thanks ds
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a457.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> is still on assignment and will remain so indefinitely.  <NAME/> Thompson will respond regarding the coding.  -  Teb
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a458.xml">
  <body>

Please contact one of the following regarding power trading:
 <NAME/> Hansen @ 853-6121  or <NAME/> Portz 853-9239  Fax number 713-646-3491
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a459.xml">
  <body>

came back from dallas friday - just went to houstons with a friend.  Saturday, worked on the house and ran some errands.  Went out saturday night and drank too much - just hung out yesterday.  Nothing at all exciting!  I am very boring these days!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a46.xml">
  <body>

I am fine with your changes to the Amendment.  Please execute two originals and forward same to my attention for final signatures.  

Many thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a460.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I have three PAA's that the North team has done.  Two people are IT.  I wasn't sure if
	that made a difference?  I told them I would see if we could get them done, but at this late date
	there were no guarantees.  If you approve, I will have <NAME/> fill out the necessary blanks.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a461.xml">
  <body>

Here is a redline and clean version of requested changes by Atmos.  If they are in agreement,  print two originals have same signed and returned to my attention.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a462.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Please change my e-mail address on your distribution list to :  dfarmer70@houston.rr.com.

Thanks.

D
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a463.xml">
  <body>

https://portal.ercot.com/PORTAL.ERCOT.COM:9999/hrnp$30000/PORTAL.ERCOT.COM:9999/Action/26011[portal]
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a464.xml">
  <body>

Can you help me figure out how to get access to this.  I get this message everyday and don't  know what to do.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a465.xml">
  <body>

FYI.  Please plan on attending this meeting for me.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a466.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I am changing my mind again on the SGA conference (typical woman)
	Call me.  <NAME/> (713) 853-7637
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a467.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
I should have been more specific;    <NAME/> is working at the Ercot ISO,  near <NAME/> Texas.    His e-mail address is below.


'bhunsucker@ercot.com'

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a468.xml">
  <body>

The capacity is set at 58000 mmbtu/d.  Please allocate with the points if it still shows up after we allocate the 
West of Thoreau group.   

If you have any questions please ask.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a469.xml">
  <body>

Who is sending the letter to let Bear Paw know we need prepayment?  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a47.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Thanks for the note and I hope your doing well.  You're right, sometimes introductions sound more like the presentation of a resume than a letter...but I think you pulled it off.

I was able to close on my condo last weekend.  It was a tremendous pain with a bit of the last minute run-around, but I finally got moved in on Friday night.  I don't know about my neighbors yet as I am the only one moved in on my floor so far.  The seller is still finishing the renovation of the place...they are converting it from an old hotel.  My condo is about 8 blocks from my office downtown, so it was great to roll out of bed this morning and be able to walk to work. 

Like you, I am not sure what <NAME/> might have told you about me...so here goes.  I was born on the east coast (Connecticut), moved around for a while, and eventually was towed out to southwest Washington by my parents.  I went to highschool in Kelso (this is where I met and then graduated with <NAME/>).  Then went to college at University of Washington in Seattle.  College was good, if a bit long.  I received a degree in Metallurgical engineering and worked as an engineer in Portland for a year doing failure and corrosion analysis (whoa!).  A bit less than 2 years ago I started working with <NAME/> as a trader, trading hourly electricity in the West.  I started out on shift, but now manage the group and get to work a more normal schedule (usually 10-12 hours a day) during the week.  I enjoy the job a ton, the market changes nearly every day and it beats the hell out of staring at a scanning electron microscope for 4 hours at a pop.

With regards to your visit.  I've been in Portland for a few years now, so I should be able to provide a fairly good guide service around the town.  Depending on when you get here and how things go,  we'll have to see if we can get you outside the city to some of the Mountains and the Coast.  Astoria is about 2 hours away and it's a pretty scenic drive out there (especially if you're from New Mexico).  If the weather's nice we might be able to check out some of the resevoirs and rivers around Mt. St. Helens and the gorge...good swimming, hiking etc.  It should be a blast. 

Have you gotten any closer to firming up when you will be in town?  I am pretty open at the start of July, and although it always rains on the 4th (EVERY single year), that's still a good time to be coming up.  Besides, if you ever thought about moving here, you have to understand why its so green...

It was good to hear from you, and if you have any questions you can give me a call at 503-887-3449.

Take care.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a470.xml">
  <body>

They should if they are dealing with transport, gas daily options,  etc. which are effected by the omicrons.  I would typically go to the leads of the respective regions, tell them which curves are unmapped and let them decide what omicron curve to use ( a lot of times they just asked the trader in charge of that point which curve to use).  

If the leads don't know what the omicron curves are the company's in trouble!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a471.xml">
  <body>

You are welcome to come down any day. 

 I think that changing the time on the 29th would be good since we are still in "bid week" that day.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a472.xml">
  <body>

JOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOONINNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii....................    

I'm ok.  I'm leaving.  Talk to you later and thanks.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a473.xml">
  <body>

Yes,  I am sorry it has been so long.  The Gty is still in our corp. offices for execution.  I will check on status tomorrow.  Thanks for your email.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a474.xml">
  <body>

I wish we could have purchased that gas at 4.18.  But, the correct price is 5.18.  I have corrected the deal ticket.

D
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a475.xml">
  <body>

Due to all the moves this week, we are canceling the staff meeting this afternoon.

	We will have a regular meeting next week.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a476.xml">
  <body>

Our Michcon and Consumers <NAME/> is iyt having a baby, so here's what he left me for Michcon and zero for Consumers.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a477.xml">
  <body>

I had a great visit with Eddie Rietze last night.  We spent about 3 hours together.  I think we should definately pursue him.
He is interested talking further.  We will probably need to meet with him during the evening.  Please let me know if I need to do 
anything to proceed.  I indicated to Eddie that you would be contacting him to set an interview schedule.

thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a478.xml">
  <body>

Yes - we will likely need to draft new product definitions as well as determine the impact on our long dated Into products.  I have a meeting w <NAME/> Nicolay at 400 to start discussing. I'll keep you updated as I learn more . Thanks.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a479.xml">
  <body>

Do you have this contract in your office.  If so, would you send  me a copy.

Thanks!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a48.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Final pricing for the subject cargo is dependent on Nov-Jan LPG prices. A provisional amount is due today. Please base the provisional amount on a Nov MB price of 35-cents, Dec and Jan MB prices of 32.5-cents. These prices reflect the current market.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a480.xml">
  <body>

I have a court at 500 - see ya there unless I here otherwise
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a481.xml">
  <body>

Is my buddy <NAME/> Allwein working with you?  If so give him a big kiss and a hug from me.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a482.xml">
  <body>

Arnie or Walt can either one of you set up conference call tomorrow with all the above mentioned and discuss
Thursdays P-2 to P-3 pig run.  Please let us know.

Thanks ds
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a483.xml">
  <body>

That's right,
I forgot about QOTSA.  Did you enjoy that CD? 
Your dad is coming in today to see the trading floor and then we are going to grab some lunch and talk about what we do here at the big E. I fly out at 4 on Friday afternoon...

I guess <NAME/> is coming to Portland at the end of October...oh-oh.

b
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a484.xml">
  <body>

Hey, I don't think you should show any cash flow for the Enbridge storage until I talk to them this afternoon.  I'm writing an email to you and a few others about what I think we should forcast and I want to talk to them first.  But between you and me, I'm thinking we show about $600,000 or so.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a485.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

The City of Glendale is ready to set up a conference call to go over the minor changes that they would like to see in the ISDA agreement.  Would you be available to do this call with them on Wednesday afternoon?  Please let me know as soon as possible if so and what time so I can set it up with the customer.

Also, they would like an electronic verson of the opinion letter.  Can you have one sent to me?

Call me if you have any questions - x30685.

Thanks,

<NAME/> <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a486.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, 
I have no idea.
I would recommend checking with <NAME/>...she's omniscient.
Good luck.

B
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a487.xml">
  <body>

We may be dining with my brother and Sister in law tomorrow around 6:30 PM.  Comments ???? Questions?????
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a488.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>

We are planning on joining Crestone for a combined <NAME/> Christmas party.  The cost for our share will be approximately $1,000.  I know it is not cheap, but I think it is an important signal and morale booster which is critical at this time.  We have a long way to go in this deal.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a489.xml">
  <body>

Chino plant 100% down = 80 MW
Bagdad plant - 50% decrease in production = 40 mw
Cerrito plant - 50% decrease in production = 40 mw

Basically 120 -150 MW offline due to PDs decrease in producion.  the same percentage decrease in gas demand is what we should see.  Let me know if you would like us to investigate this further.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a49.xml">
  <body>

http://salon.com/politics/feature/2002/02/08/enron_list/index.html
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a490.xml">
  <body>

I will be in Chicago Thursday and Friday.  I will need to leave for the airport around 3:00.  Please let me know if you would like for me to call in.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a491.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>:
 
The topic will be "Storage".  Would you please confirm that it is on Thursday, October 4, 2001.  I'm out of the office tomorrow so I will have to put a presentation together on Wednesday and Thursday.
 
    Thanks,  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a492.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> and I agree.  The 567,546.5 is the same number we came up with.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a493.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Per our conversation, the following are the fuel management team's assumptions of fuel requirements for Eco at 100% of capacity:

LNG   91,260 MMBtu/day at 507 MW    Heat Rate = 7500 BTU/kwh

LPG   1905 Metric Tons at 507 MW     Heat Rate = 7461 BTU/kwh    (Note: 522 gallons/MT   ,   91,300 Btu/gallon)

No.2   619,000 gallons/day at 465 MW   Heat Rate = 7313 BTU/kwh    (Note: 131,850 Btu/gallon)


Heat rates at less than 100% of capacity will be different from those at 100%. Check with <NAME/> or <NAME/> regarding performance curves.

Call me if you have any additional questions.


Regards,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a494.xml">
  <body>

Here is a little more info in the Tenn/Sonat park & loan deal.  The volume is 500,195 dth parked in Bear Creek storage on Tenn contract 15692.  It was suppossed to come out on Sonat this month but we never scheduled it.  Yesterday, <NAME/> Garcia tried to schedule some of this gas for today's gas day.  We don't know if Tenn allowed us to schedule it yet.

<NAME/>
There is only 1 Tenn park & loan deal for 500,195
2 Cgas park & loan deals shown below.  We have not scheduled any of the CGAS park & loan deals.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a495.xml">
  <body>

>    A boss and two of his employees are on their way to a meeting. Walking
> through a park, they find a miracle lamp. They rub it and suddenly a genie
> appears.
>    The genie says: "Normally, the one who frees me, has three wishes free.
> Now, you are three persons, so everyone of you has one wish." The first
> employee yells: "Me first, ME FIRST!!!" and expresses his wish: "I would
> like to be on the Bahamas, on a very fast yacht, and have no more worries"
> And pfffffff, he is away.
>    Now the second employee yells: "Me next, ME NEXT" and he expresses his
> wish: "I would like to be in the Caribbean, along with the prettiest girls
> of the world, and an inexhaustible source of exotic cocktails." And
> pfffffff, he is away.
>    "And what is your wish?" the genie asks the boss.
>    And the boss replies:
>    "I want these two idiots to be back in office after lunch!!!"
>    And the moral of this story: Always let your boss speak first!!!!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a496.xml">
  <body>

Shubh,

How are you doing through all of the uncertainty associated with DPC these days? Are we still waiting for the lenders to decide whether or not they will continue funding the project? What is the MSEB's current position?

I'll give you a call Wednesday morning (Mumbai time).

Best Regards,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a497.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>'t know what you think, but <NAME/> Sheik is playing at the Mucky Duck tomorrow night...Thurs could work for me too, we'll see.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a498.xml">
  <body>

HOW WAS THE TRADITION COURSE?

ARE YOU GOLFED OUT YET?    I DIDNT DO ANYTHING SATURDAY NIGHT.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a499.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,
Try to make sure you get these to me rather than to my Dad.  I think he is starting to get annoyed.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a5.xml">
  <body>

Our current cash balance with Reliant is $52,850.00.  We did not request any gas for tomorrow under the swing arrangements.  I have requested a wire in the amount of $22,000.00 to be made on Friday April 12th.

<NAME/>, I had to move the payment to Friday because some <NAME/> "approval" people are out of the office but we have a large cash balance and it shouldn't be a problem if it gets delayed untill Monday.

Also, <NAME/> Wheeler discovered an error in my worksheet that impacted the cash balance effective March 1st forward.  My worksheet is set up so that any change in a volume or price for a prior month will change the current cash balance.  I will keep track of all changes at the bottom of the Summary worksheet in this file.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a50.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, how long has this been a problem?  Is there a concern we have caused
	customers problems in nominating due to bad information?  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a500.xml">
  <body>

I reserved a court for 500.  Let me know in the afternoon if you can make it. See ya.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a501.xml">
  <body>

Yes, we want the name on the contract to be Atoms Energy Corporation.  Let me know if you want to make and changes to the numbers.  Thanks!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a502.xml">
  <body>

I am a proud papa!  She's so cute too!

What are you doing in CT?  I thougt you were in  CA?

Things are going ok for me.  Me and my "Woman" (we are not married - yet) are living in an apartment near Kirby and Westheimer.  I'm tired all the time anymore - not from staying up with the baby, that's woman's work.  I'm reading a <NAME/> Clancy book and I can't put it down.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a503.xml">
  <body>

Group,

I received a call from <NAME/> McReynold at the BPA today.  <NAME/> was concerned with the level of service that our group is providing.  <NAME/> explained to me the necessity and importance of calling in and reporting the actual amount of energy generated by Grays Harbor and Frontier EVERY hour.  The group at BPA cannot close their accounting books and meet reliability performance measures without our information.  I am meeting with <NAME/> on Tuesday.  <NAME/> is inclined to recommend to BPA that we are incapable of this service because of our inconsistent performance.  Such a recommendation would severely limit <NAME/>'s ability to produce value for our service customers in the near term and would likely prevent us from attracting new customers.  I believe that we can provide <NAME/>'s group with the information that it needs with minimal impact to our trading.

Therefore: 

We must call Grays Harbor and Frontier at the top of EVERY hour.  Then we need to call BPA and communicate the ACTUAL energy generated, not an estimate.  Finally, sign off the hour in the services book.  <NAME/> has provided us with the needed information for each day. Reserves can only be used for the hour that we are in, than we must resupply the schedule from a different source by working with the BPA marketers. If you have a question regarding reserves or pulling a schedule--please call <NAME/> or me.

If this process takes more than 5 minutes, please let me know. It is each trader's responsibilty to make this work.  It should be noted that we need to do this even if the generator is prescheduled, and must to continue to do this until these generators are automatically metered.  And yes, we will be compensated by the Services desk for our work. 

This service is a priority and should be treated as such.

Please see me with your comments and concerns regarding this job function.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a504.xml">
  <body>

This is interesting news.  Thought you might want to know.  
I sent him pressures on TW side for the month of may per his request.

ds
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a505.xml">
  <body>

why don't you figure out what the heck you're doing before you try to rope me into something
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a506.xml">
  <body>

Ask <NAME/> or whoever looks at Tenn if they are interested in any Iroq / Tenn capacity.  The capacity goes from Tcpl/Iroq - Wadd to Iroq/Tenn - Wright, then from Iroq/Tenn - Wright to Mendon and Boston Gas citygate.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a507.xml">
  <body>

What's up with BHP?  HESCO?  I was gone most of friday and feel like I was gone longer.  Call me when you get a chance.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a508.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

The confirmation group will resend the confirms and it does look like we will need you guys to sign them and fax them back to us.  Our fax number is listed below.  Let me know if you need anything else.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a509.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

I am using the cellular phone mentioned in your note. My Company Number is 1105 and my RC is 120588. 

Regards,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a51.xml">
  <body>

I will have 4 books:

CAND-MGMT-BAS for all AECO and DAWN BASIS
CAND-MGMT-GD for fixed price AECO and DAWN 
CAND-MGMT-PR for NYMEX
CAND-MGMT-PWR fot <NAME/>, MID-C, Ontario, NY, NEPOOL, PJM, Cinergy power
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a510.xml">
  <body>

These lists could change before the new company opens for business.


Execute for all gas products, read only for power and access to stack manager:
<NAME/> Shively
<NAME/> Storey
<NAME/> Ruscitti
<NAME/> Cuilla
<NAME/> <NAME/>
<NAME/> <NAME/>
<NAME/> Simpson

Read only for all gas and power products:
<NAME/> Luce
<NAME/> Thurston
<NAME/> Frihart
<NAME/> Murrell
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a511.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, do you keep track of the Phoneburst list?  Let's discuss in the morning.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a512.xml">
  <body>

Please give me a call to discuss their confirmation.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a513.xml">
  <body>

Can someone do a study on the tariffs of major pipeline storage fields to determine which fields require that storage gas is withdrawn regardless of price.  If not, how much to roll storage?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a514.xml">
  <body>

I will let you know any updates.  We will be allocating until further notice.
San <NAME/>:         800,000
Thoreau West  1010,000
 

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a515.xml">
  <body>

this sucks....can't nom until the internet's up
 
how much would someone have s**t bricks if'd i'd made the same request....actually, the thought of that email response (or lack thereof) is making me laugh right now.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a516.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Walt is saying the field would just tap the line and install a block valve. Can you talk to Sammie <NAME/> and make sure that you both agree regarding the EFM.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a517.xml">
  <body>

Sorry to hear it man. It has not been a great last couple of months.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a518.xml">
  <body>

The attached will be the operating situations that we will cover.

<NAME/> if you see anything that we need to revise before, please call.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a52.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I would like to order the BlackBerry.  My ID No. is 10028029.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a53.xml">
  <body>

Concerning the above, please see the attached Confirm / GTC for each.  Please give me a call if you have any questions.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a54.xml">
  <body>

If Chattahoochee converted all of their SFTS  to FTS-1 for the purpose of release, there is no problem with a gap.  If they still hold any SFTS,  they cannot have FTS-1 capacity at the same time, even for 1 month.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a55.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, have you been keeping track of  the people responding to the invitation?
	Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a56.xml">
  <body>

Here is the draft.  Prior to sending to customer, <NAME/> please look at the MAC language and advise is it needs to be reworded.  Also, is this a political sub-division? If so, I will need to add a provision for same.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a57.xml">
  <body>

The supply from the desk-to-desk transaction (#1075281) is pathed to the transport.  The 1023 contract is an ENA agreement.  So, deal 1075281 transfers the gas to ENA.  ENA then transports the gas on it's agreement on Lone Star.

D
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a58.xml">
  <body>

FYI.  Just wanted to be sure everyone had a copy of this letter.  In relation
to this letter we had a posting go out on the WEB.  Please be sure everyone
on the team has read this notice.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a59.xml">
  <body>

Is this a new contract on our side to send to them for review?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a6.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, as discussed attached is a revised GISB for your execution.  Please print two originals sign and return same to my attention at the address listed below.  Should you have any additional questions, please do not hesitate to give me a call.  Upon final signature, I will forward an original for your records.   


  

Regards,
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a60.xml">
  <body>

I will be here Tuesday only this week.  Tuesday works for me.

ds
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a61.xml">
  <body>

You can go ahead and talk to <NAME/>...Also, how was you vaca?
And I have some things for you to take care of from Thursday and this weekend when you have a chance.
Thanks,

B
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a62.xml">
  <body>

Here is the amendment for the above. Please forward to your contact.
 
Thanks !
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a63.xml">
  <body>

Thought I would ask a more specific question.  Do you know of any transactions which <NAME/> may be in default due to recent circumstances?  I'm excluding trading deals.  Maybe some of the asset management deals?  Joint venture companies (enovate?)?

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a64.xml">
  <body>

hey <NAME/>, 

Let's do lunch next week.  We are moving into the new building this weekend.  I'll be able to show you around (if I'm still here).

We had a tough football weekend.  It's about time we got beat.  We didn't deserve the wins we had.  Anyway, I've got to get to work.  Trying to break $12.00 today.  It's kind of odd...moving into a brand new building when your stock price has reached an all-time low...

D
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a65.xml">
  <body>

No they did not make our changes.  AES is requesting a contract.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a66.xml">
  <body>

Attached is the additional confirm NG would like to move from Heartland.  Are you ok with this?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a67.xml">
  <body>

absolutely nothing.  Just working on whatever I can.  very slow.  what about you?  what are you doing thanksgiving?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a68.xml">
  <body>

if you're on the internet, call me when you are off.....

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a69.xml">
  <body>

Hey.  I went on a company outing to Aransas Pass last week.  Left Wed afternoon and got back Friday afternoon.  One of the pipelines I deal with has a hunting and fishing lodge down there.  It was nice.  I caught 2 redfish - both keepers too!  The guide would bait my hook and throw it in the water.  All I had to do was sit there and look pretty till the fish started biting.  I could really get used to that sort of thing.

The fishing guide said I should expect to pay about $1,000/ft for my fishing boat.  I guess my boat will only be about 4 ft long.   Keep looking for my BOAT.

Let's see - the ex wife came in from <NAME/> for a wedding Friday night.  She stayed with me all weekend.  I took her to the airport this morining.  Things went pretty well - no romance, just good friends.  I introduced her to my girlfriend - we all had lunch together.  That was a little odd.

Nothing else going on.  I'll try to have an update on the legal stuff by Wed.

Later Gator.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a7.xml">
  <body>

Shemin and I are going to lunch on Monday.  She might even PAY!!!!!  I told her I was going to bring 12 of my closest friends.  Well, I don't have any friends but I told her that you two might like to go.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a70.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

I tried to phone you at your office and your cellular but could not reach you. Please e-mail me with your new contact numbers.

I hope that you are doing well and enjoying your new role.

Regards,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a71.xml">
  <body>

Group,
I have copied in a note from <NAME/> at EPE. As you can see they are placing a VERY high importance on economic dispatch of the units. Please be aware that every move with regards to marketing and running their system is under EXTREME scrutiny.

Please call me before you call our customer.

Thanks,
<NAME/>



Correction:
The burner problem is on Newman 3.  (Thank You! Mr <NAME/>)   The unit will be held at 85 MW's until repairs can be made.  The plan is to assess the problem Monday morning and make the necessary repairs.    

If prices continue to be below cost we need to purchase power and back down
local units.  With Copper off, the dispatch shows we need to purchase power for 5 or 6 hours through super peak. 

Depending on load,  GT 1 and GT 2 should be put in the hole (around 7 to 10
MW's each) HE 1:00 through HE 9:00...

If  Market conditions are less than $14.00  BACK DOWN Four Corners...   As
load picks up be sure to pick up Four Corners first!
If there is a reason we have to dump FC power please send me a note!   If
there is any confusion over whether to back down FC CALL.

Any questions or comments please call at  5808  or  915-204-1202...
 
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a72.xml">
  <body>

Well I hope he puts in a good word for me.

I talked to <NAME/>, and he didn't say anything about the call you referenced.  Are you sure your leg wasn't being pulled?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a73.xml">
  <body>

Actually,
I think the Honda is probably the one.  Much cooler...and good Honda reliability.  Looks good in Silver or Red.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a74.xml">
  <body>

I have sold Frontera the following:

he 7 - 200 mw for $26.04
he 8 - 50 mw for $26.04


Please transfer this imbalance amount to me.    See deal no's   835119 & 835120.


Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a75.xml">
  <body>

Toby, thanks for the way you sent this note to folks.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a76.xml">
  <body>

Recommendation for ENA Pools
1st choice  Terminate pools and producer contracts on 12/3/01, no cash flow and everything is pre-petition.
2nd choice Terminate pools and producer contracts on 12/31/01 and deal with one month's cash flow
3rd choice  Terminate pools as soon as possible to eliminate the administrative effort involved.

I've been trying to determine the EES imbalances on Dominion and I'm not having much luck.  Dominion gave me the ENA balances over the phone.  When I called back a day later to get the EES balances, I was told to submit a written request to <NAME/> Saviers, Dominion's in house counsel.  I have not done that.  I would prefer that Dominion provide us a written document stating what the pool balances are as of 11/30/01 and 12/31/01.  

Based on the pool balances below, I would recommend terminating the ENA pools effective 12/3/01 assuming the following.
	1.  Producer payments for Oct and Nov have not been made and go into the pre-petition bucket.
	2.  ENA owes Dominion gas which is also pre-petition.
	3.  The producers will be able to reallocate their gas for December forward to another marketer's pool.

Items to consider
If we terminate the pools on 12/31/01 or later, ENA will need to sell the imbalance gas and pay the producers.  Dominion will need to provide ENA a method to do this if the pools are terminated.  I would recommend paying the producers after we collect the money for selling the imbalance gas AND after we pay Dominion any gathering/transporting charges associated with those balances.  The volumes are small so ENA will not see much economic benefit from this process.  Also, the administrative effort involved is VERY VERY HIGH due to the small volumes per producer.

Dominion will prefer to cancel the pools with a 0 or positive imbalance.  On 12/3/01, ENA will still have a negative cumulative imbalance.

Most of the producers have not been paid for Oct or Nov 2001 activity.  I assume that since those dollars go into a pre-petition bucket that we should not terminate any producer contracts before 12/3/01.

	
3/5/02 Per <NAME/> Coen at Dominion
ENA Pool Balances as of
			11/30/01	12/31/01	
Gath North		1,323		2,187		
Tran North		0		0
Gath South		(26,482)		31,583
Tran South		5,412		8,143

Cumulative		(19,747)		41,913


Dominion IF Prices
Mar 2002	$2.59
Feb 2002	$2.20
Jan 2002	$2.79
Dec 2001	$2.42
Nov 2001	$3.37
Oct 2001	$2.02
Sep 2001	$2.42
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a77.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Attached are two copies of the revised ISDA - one is redlined and one is not.  If you are ready for an executable copy, please let me know and I will have them printed out and sent to you.  <NAME/> Shackleton is on vacation this week but <NAME/> Heard is trying to start the process for outside counsil opinion. I will keep you informed as I know more about this.  Please let me know if you have any questions or need anything at all from me.

Thanks!

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a78.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/> and <NAME/>, thank you so much for the invitation, but I will be at the
	NNG Customer meeting in Kansas City otherwise I would plan on attending.
	Have a great time.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a79.xml">
  <body>

hey...

i actually just filled my change of address form out this morning...i figured you'd already done yours.  i'm leaving for the airport straight from work tonight and don't get back until sunday night.  i can fill it out monday, but if you would like it done before then you may want to try and tap someone else for the job.

the reason monday is important is b/c someone wants to rent our place and i've told the complex that i'll be completely out by the end of the day monday.  so starting monday night i'm back in northwest houston and w/out a mail key.  on the bright side, i'm getting a fair amount of money back from the january rent (which means we're cool rent wise, i.e. you needn't give me any $ for january).  

i do have an interview in seattle tomorrow morning...i'm nervous and excited.  i've been studying a bunch for the last week and a half or so to try and prep myself.  i think i'm more nervous about not liking the job rather that liking it or not doing well in the interview.  also, i'm going to see "kiss me kate" the musical w/ my friend up there so that should be fun.

i'm glad to hear that things seem to be going so well for you there, you sound awfully busy.  keep us posted on all your many activities.  

<NAME/>

-- i knew you were going to take like a fish to water w/ this thing.....never should've worried so much.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a8.xml">
  <body>

I have sold Frontera a financial swap for $28.50 for hours ending 7-12.    The first 3 hours are for size (300 mw's).  
I would buy hours 7-9 tomorrow for up to $20.      I could buy up to the 300 mw's.     Schedule this to load in the North.
I could also use 200 mw's for he 10 and 150 mw's for he 11.

Calpine has had an offer recently for hours ending 7-9.

If you have questions,  please give me a call,  as this is a very important issue.

Words of advice:

Dont go into the market with a $20 bid for 300 mw's.   Quietly accumulate these mw's if possible.     Do not tip your hand on this deal,  as that would contribute to spiking RT prices.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a80.xml">
  <body>

Give me your fax number and I'll fax it over.  <NAME/> Sewell said he would not pay for it as ENA and I don't know enough about the deal to argue with him.  I've pasted in <NAME/>'s response is in black below.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a81.xml">
  <body>

Sell 50 June, 2001 NYMEX Contracts @ $ 4.35
Sell 100 July, 2001 NYMEX Contracts @ $ 4.415

Current Open Positions:   June, 2001 Short 150 Contracts,   July, 2001 Short 100 Contracts

Settlements :   June, 2001    $4.348,    July, 2001 $4.414
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a82.xml">
  <body>

Hey <NAME/>,

That deal should have been booked to Nine Energy Services, LLC.  Can you please change that in Sitara.....thanks!
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a83.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Attached is our response to your request for a description of the steps <NAME/> is taking to improve flows to the Griffith power plant.  Please let me know if you have any questions.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a84.xml">
  <body>

can you make it more official looking, ideally a fax, signed by you, no worries, there is no liability
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a85.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>,

It looks as if we're going to be trading effective Mon (2/11).  I'm looking for some assurance that we'll have at least the basics ready to go with regard to position manager.  Can you update?  Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a86.xml">
  <body>

Here is the amendment for Aspect.  Please add the Meter No. to Schedule I for the new well.  Please let me know if you have any questions.

  
 dp
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a87.xml">
  <body>

Thanks for the work <NAME/>.
I will see you on the 27th at PDX.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a88.xml">
  <body>

Guys, very good notes for the weekend.  Appreciate the comments. It helps alot when preparing
	<NAME/> for the Monday morning (<NAME/>) meeting.  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a89.xml">
  <body>

Hey!  Glad to hear you are well.  I have thought about our days on the 92nd floor as well.  Had some acquaintances that worked for Cantor as well as a close friend who worked for them that was called back to <NAME/> for a meeting that very morning. Very glad he is with us today!  

It is cool that you hired Palmore.  You will have to tell him hello for me.  I did come back to <NAME/> in January.  <NAME/> brought me back to peddle gas in the West US.  Nothing much new in my life, just a new house and job - but I am glad to be back.  I miss the outdoor life in Portland but the people here are so much more fun and nice!  If you are ever in town - you better have a beer with me!  I will let you know if I am in Dallas -
Take care,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a9.xml">
  <body>

Wow...I must say this was the last thing I expected you to be emailing me about.  I'll try and give you a call after work ( around 4:30 or so ) if you want to talk about it some more, just let me know.  I do think it's good that you guys are at least talking about all this stuff regardless of what you decide is the right for both of you.  

Sorry to hear about <NAME/>...that is horrible.  What brings on shingles anyway?  I thought it has something to do with stress, but I could be totally off.

Glad you like the CD...I've been listening to it non-stop.  I'm totally empowered after "I'm Alright" and then plunge into super-reflective mode with "Wildest Dreams".  Get on the <NAME/> Richey web site and read the lyrics and you'll understand why.  By the way, she's playing at Stubb's on June 14th and in <NAME/> at The Fabulous Satellite Lounge on the 16th....food for thought.

As for my call, there was some news...he contacted me around 10 am or so and we chatted throughout the day.  I'll tell you more about it when I call, but you're only going to be a bigger fan.  That of course is the problem I'm having.

Talk to you soon,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a90.xml">
  <body>

Please see the attached site.     The logon for this is:     ljester  
				 password is:  38zpzz

http://oasis.ercot-iso.com/index.html

You can copy existing Oasis requests or create new.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a91.xml">
  <body>

<NAME/>, I'll be glad to lead the discussion.  Is this informal or do I have to
	have a formal presentation?  Thanks. <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a92.xml">
  <body>

Here is the contract,  I am still working on the confirm.  Do you want me to send the contract/confirm to the customer or will you?
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a93.xml">
  <body>

Jerry,
Please see the attached .     As I mentioned,   I will be out of the office visiting Ercot tomorrow.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a94.xml">
  <body>

We don't have a deadline.  Our lawyers are scattered pretty thin.  What would probably happen is that you guys might show me a bid for some of the capacity, then we would have to talk to the pipelines and see what they want to do.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a95.xml">
  <body>

Thanks for this - it is very helpful.  It seeme to have taken everybody by surprise even regulatory.  Have a great weekend and I will talk to you next week.
 
ps on the midmarket change .... I'll circle the wagons as long as necessary.  No way, no how, no reallocation.  In the East, we allocate work based on project not client base.  The West will likely be the same but .. thanks for the heads up so we can react in the most thoughtful of ways.
 
pss on the secretary front, I've been exchanging messages with <NAME/> so I can get the facts and unanimous approval - I'll try to get MH's OK next weekend.  <NAME/> call when accomplished.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a96.xml">
  <body>

That sounds good to me.
I appreciate your help.
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a97.xml">
  <body>

why the heck am I getting all the crap on this one....I'm not the one who came back to the table with puke on myself.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a98.xml">
  <body>

thankyou very much.. I need to reschedule our meeting.  Any day next week works for me, after 2:30pm.
</body>
</text>

<text file="SmallValid//a99.xml">
  <body>

Hi,

I was a guest in your hotel on December 30th through January 1st, 2002.  I wonder if I left behind a pair of cranberry colored womens' ankle length boots (sized 8.5)  My room number was 1965.  Please respond via e-mail or by telephone.  My work number is 713-853-5772.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

</testing>
