<training>
<text file="Verify2Train//a1.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

I am disappointed on the timing but I understand.  Thanks.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a10.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

I am stuck in London.  I will attend either in person or by video from our London office.
 
<NAME/> Haedicke
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a11.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

I am stuck in London -- hope to get out  Sunday.  Nice to hear from you.
 
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a12.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

I think it is something we watch closely as you suggest.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a13.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>:  It has been 120 days for voice mail that is not deleted.  It should be further reduced to 7 days.  
 
<NAME/> Haedicke
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a14.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Is there anything I need to work on tonight?  What is the schedule tonight?  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a15.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/> and <NAME/>:

The Wholesale legal conference is coming up soon.  I wanted to get a head count and the names of the attendees from each of you.  For planning purposes, I have assumed 5 lawyers from each of your groups.  Let me know.  Also, are there any European or South American topics you would suggest we cover?  So far, we have Whalley and Frevert signed up to give us a business update.

Regards,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a16.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

I am fine with the agenda except that I will have E. Sager talk about the trading forms.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a17.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Thanks!  Yes, please keep me off the Section 16 list!   <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a18.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

That makes sense.  How do we notify our trading counterparties?  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a19.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>:  Thanks for raising that question because it is very important that we are coordinated.  I have forwarded this question on to Jordan and I think he and I need to work together on this matter.  Perhaps the three of us should get on the telephone to resolve.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a2.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Should we try Akin Gump?  What is your recommendation off the list?  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a20.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Coordination is a major problem at <NAME/>.  You are asking all the right questions.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a21.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>, I do not think I am going to nyc.  Love Dad
<NAME/> Haedicke
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a22.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>:  The last sentence was changed to "we expect you to perform".   <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a23.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Thanks for the offer.  I cannot use them either.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a24.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/> and I will cover the suggested topics.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a25.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

[Haedicke, <NAME/> E.] J , please arrange for a meeting.  It is ok for it to be lunch.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a26.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Thanks for inviting me.  I unfortunately will not be able to attend.

Regards,

<NAME/> Haedicke
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a27.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

I have a few thoughts on the offsite.  I think we could have a theme of restructuring and change.  We would have to make sure it is forward looking and upbeat in that we have learned a lot that will make us better in the future.  The presentations could include the following:

1.   What we learned in CA -- Sager
2.   Preparing for workouts -- Mellencamp
3.   Lessons learned in international -- Lundstrom
4.   Deregulation of energy markets -- Kean/Shapiro
5.   Managing Legal Risks -- Haedicke
6.   Executives -- Frevert and Whalley
7.   Europe presentation
8.   Retail presentation
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a28.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>:

Congratulations!  We will need to talk about some additional coordination.  Let me know when is convenient for you. 

 <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a29.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>:  I talked to <NAME/> and we have worked through a revised strategy as we talked about yesterday.  So no call from <NAME/>.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a3.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>:  I want to put Aronowitz for ENA as well as EGM.  He will get an assist from Sager but he will lead.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a30.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Please join me for a baseball game.  The Astros are playing the NY Mets on Wednesday, August, 1.  The game starts at 7:05 p.m.  

Please RSVP to <NAME/> by e-mail to let her know if you will be able to attend.  (Unfortunately due to the limited number of seats available in a suite, we were not able to extend this invitation to your spouse or significant other.)

<NAME/> to see you there!
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a31.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Stacy:

I would like to know who on the committee is willing to spend time and resources on what issues.  I think that is critical.  Thanks.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a32.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Sami:  Please set some time on my schedule tomorrow to talk this through.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a33.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

It can wait his return.  Please ask him if he is available to speak on Dec 4 at the conference.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a34.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

We will get you a summary soon.  <NAME/>
<NAME/> Haedicke
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a35.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>:  <NAME/> Taylor and I can get this done through <NAME/> Net Works.  Thanks.   <NAME/> Haedicke
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a36.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>:  There is a conflict of interest in Thompson having all the info and selling to a group formed by him and other employees.  We need to talk this through.  Maybe, he should take a leave of absence.  Should <NAME/> negotiate the deal for ENA?  Selling to employees is sensitive now.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a37.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Thanks for the offer, but otherwise occupied.  
 
Regards,
 
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a38.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Just do the best you can.  We will probably end up moving it to a different day.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a39.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Did we talk about the cap on breakage fee?
<NAME/> Haedicke
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a4.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Dear <NAME/>:

I am proud of MSU and would like to help.  I will ask my assistant to set up a time for us to talk through your questions over the next week.

Regards,

<NAME/> Haedicke
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a40.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Thanks for the message.  I would e-mail <NAME/> Aronowitz.  Regards,  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a41.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Sami, by copy hereof, I have asked <NAME/> Hodge to look into this matter.  He is at 36911.   <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a42.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

I need to talk through our cash position for tomorrow at with our contingency team. I would like to do it today at 4:30 pm central time. <NAME/> Haedicke
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a43.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

J:  Please forward this on to the <NAME/> employees that plan events.  Shira is a family friend and I would recommend her.  Also give me a status report.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a44.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>, <NAME/>, <NAME/>: Do you have any comments on the agenda?  Let me know and I will forward them on.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a45.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Where did we come out on a cap on breakage fee?
<NAME/> Haedicke
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a46.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

I am ok so long as the firm would never pursue litigation against <NAME/> -- on that basis I would grant the waiver.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a47.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>, thanks for the message.  I think, I would like to plan a trip and discuss the issues in person at GE.  Early October would work for me.

Regards,

<NAME/> Haedicke
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a48.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

I want to go through a list of each counterparty we think is going to go into bankruptcy and what we are doing to prepare for that.  Thanks.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a49.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Good luck.  I will email you later.  Dad
<NAME/> Haedicke
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a5.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>:  Does the RTO order require a task force to draft new language?  Let me know.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a50.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Yes, so long as they are employees and not on contract.  Move them to <NAME/> Schuler's group.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a51.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

Per our conversation yesterday, I propose we send out the following memo:

In order to better coordinate the various west coast power matters, effective immediately, <NAME/> Steffes and <NAME/> Sanders will jointly take the lead role.  <NAME/> and <NAME/> will be responsible for preparing a comphrehensive strategy for all the matters, reviewing the strategy with the California Committee and seeking approval of the California Committee before taking any material action.  Please do all you can to assist <NAME/> and <NAME/> on the west coast power matters.

I would copy only the people working on these matters including Steffes, Sanders, Belden, Mellencamp, Shapiro, Sharp, <NAME/>, Tribolet, Lavorato and Delainey.
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a52.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>:  Can you look into this while <NAME/> is out of the office.
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a53.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

I will be on the telephone on this one because of a management meeting the same day.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a54.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>:

This is a tough battle.  It may be worse because your clients are either the same ones or geographically very close.  I would try to address it by pointing out the limitations of the simplier forms and as a fallback emphasize the increased risk (legal and otherwise) when using the shorter forms.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a55.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>:

<NAME/> is scheduled to speak on Friday, October 12 at 8:30 am for 30-45 minutes.  No slides are necessary.  The lawyers will be interested in where <NAME/> sees the growth in the company and where the business is strong.  There will be Q&A and I think he will get some good questions.  Some possible questions:  What does <NAME/> expect from the legal department?  How will the attacks impact on our business?  What will be his focus in his new job?  It should be a very friendly crowd -- since <NAME/> knows most of the lawyers and they know him.

I miss you too!  

<NAME/> Haedicke
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a6.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>, in the Dunn Committee case, we just got a great order in our favor out of the courts.  We need to try to leverage off this order to slow down the AG.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a7.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

J, please get this message ready to send from me to the Specialists.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a8.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>/<NAME/>:

Have we put the updated netting language in the contract?  Would it ever come into play?

Regards,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify2Train//a9.xml">
 <author id="655437"/>
  <body>

There are some more developments re <NAME/> that we should talk about.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

</training>
