<training>
<text file="Verify3Train//a1.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

I have made note to your new email address.

When I make it over to London again, you will be one of the first that I contact.  Could you send me your home number and address?

Great luck running the search firm,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a10.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Attached is a list of your rec and del points on 27161 as of Nov 1, 2001.

If you disagree with it or want to discuss some realignments, let me know.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a11.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

If you have any problems, let me know.  Otherwise, we'll talk later on how to resolve this.

<NAME/>

http://www.tw.enron.com/twtariff/et_tf_curr_vol_frame.html


Look at sheets 70 and 145-152
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a12.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

I'd like to sign up for the ClickatHome service.  I have seen the Terms and Conditions and the Election Agreement but I haven't come across a way to sign up.  Please let me know how to sign up and order the equipment.

Thank you,
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a13.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Please book room 1336 for a meeting with Reliant on Wednesday Dec 5 at 2:00 until 3:30.

If it is already booked, please let me know.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a14.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Howdy from Texas.

I am writing to see if you know where <NAME/> has landed since the reorg. of EBS.  I'm glad to see you still have an <NAME/> address.  

I was telling a friend about our trip to Denmark and that museum that we saw there.  

Please let me know if you know where <NAME/> is.

<NAME/> all is well,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a15.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

It just goes to show.... If you just keep winning, things usually work out.  Good luck at Texas Stadium.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a16.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

I can't remember if I responded to you....I took vacation all last week.

Things are fine in my little corner (as good as can be expected).  A bit sad for a lot of other people around here.

As soon as I get caught up, I'll give you a call.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a17.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

This is an asset purchase (a mothballed oil pipeline for conversion to nat gas).  <NAME/> Guthrie did not attend.
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a18.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

Please look at the attached.  If there are some things missing, please let me know.  If some things on the list are not applicable, please note that too. Just send your deletions/additions to me via email.  If you can get this to me by the end of the day Wednesday, that would allow us to proceed with Questar all the sooner.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a19.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

Thanks <NAME/>, I'll call the guy.  If I need any more information, I'll let you know.  Thanks also for doing this so quickly.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a2.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>

 
 
<NAME/> Chronicle Online
ID:         10122822
PW:         -NA-
 
 
www.dslreports.com
ID:         markmc
PW:         121212
 
 
Dallas Morning News
      ID:         -NA-
      PW:         boomer
 
 
 http://djinteractive.com
      ID:         enemmcconn
      PW:         70450689
 
Caminus Zai*net
      ID:         mmcconnell
      PW:         switch
 
 
ECInside
      ID:
      PW:         sarah
 
Netscape Quicktime   
      ID:         mcconnellmarkr
      PW:         sarah
 
<http://www.ebs-broadband.net/index.asp>
      ID:         Enr161
      PW:         FYI21502
            -or-
ID:         Enr123
PW:         FYI18447
 
<NAME/>
      ID:         p00405823
      PW:         121212
 
Expedia.com
ID:         fallguy344
      PW:         
 
http://pavdata.com/Downloads/Security/index.html
ID:                downloads
PW:                 downloads
 
Amazon.com
      ID:         
PW:         868686
 
The Economist
      ID:         mrmcconnell 
      PW:         121212
 
TW Deal Profit/Analysis Tools
ID:         kchow 
      PW:         kctw1
 
EnronOnline
ID:         MMCCONNE    
      PW:         TWMM7896    
 
<NAME/>
      ID:         90043797
      PW:         121212
 
Paine Webber
      ID:         PWZXD8XDYPB
      PW:         6158
 
EPOCH Partners
      ID:
      PW:         ramie
 
Classmates.com
      ID:         97970801
      PW:         mustang
 
<NAME/> Presentation Library
ID:         mmcconnell  
      PW:         121212
 
American Auto Association
ID:         sarahhm     
      PW:         12121212
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a20.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

Yeah,  Baylor this weekend and Nebraska next.  This Baylor game is coming at the right time.  Good luck with Colorado.
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a21.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Thanks for the email.  I enjoyed the evening in <NAME/> as well.  I also enjoyed the game vs KSU.

Your resume looks very impressive.  I would continue to work through the university and make sure that you get on the interview schedule when we come back up.

I'll hold on to your resume and pass it on to people in the pipeline group that may be looking for an intern.

Best of luck,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a22.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

We'll get that for you.  We are awaiting a call back from Questar to confirm out days in the data room.  This coming week looks doubtful.  We'll be in touch.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a23.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

Attached are the electronic versions.  At the very least, the underline needs to be removed from the changed sentences.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a24.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

With some kind guidance from the veterans around here, I'd be glad to do it.  If it can wait a couple of days.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a25.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

Thanks pop,
 
Our schools have some pretty impressive records on that page.
 
By the way, that NCAA site is pretty interesting if you ever get bored.
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a26.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Attached are the links to the places <NAME/> and I went.

Private game reserve		http://www.singita.com/lodges/

Private game reserve		http://www.ccafrica.com/destinations/southafrica/phinda/accomrock.asp

<NAME/> Lodge (enrvironmental)	http://www.cybele.co.za/
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a27.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

Thanks <NAME/>.  I won't be able to participate because I will be at the OU/Texas game.  (Boomer Sooner).
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a28.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

Let's talk about it tonight.   I certainly don't mind a smaller Christmas.  I'm worried about what Ramie thinks.
 
 
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a29.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

When: Tuesday, October 09, 2001 2:30 PM-3:30 PM (GMT-06:00) Central Time (US & Canada).
Where: tbd

*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*

Update on Status, review critical assumptions, strategize on economics
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a3.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

Monday night and Tuesday?  <NAME/> got a special deal to play golf for half price at a nice course in San <NAME/>.  I told him yes but I needed to check with you.  I moved our Hoffman meeting back to 5:00 on Tuesday.   I still am committed to play golf on Wednesday as well.  Let me know if this interferes with any plans or if you don't think you'll be seeing enough of me.

smoootch

ps  I've left a message for <NAME/> with the receptionist from his group.  I still don't know if he is here.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a30.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

When: Wednesday, December 05, 2001 2:00 PM-3:00 PM (GMT-06:00) Central Time (US & Canada).
Where: EB1336

*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a31.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,
 
Welcome to <NAME/>!  
 
 
We will immediately start the "development" program to instill the <NAME/> viewpoint....We are the best and brightest employees and we are better and smarter than any company in the world.  We are the elite.
 
Just kidding.  I look forward to seeing you in the elevator banks.
 
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a32.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Hey!  Just thinking about you.  I hope all is well out west.  Things here are sure interesting.  You should be very happy that you are not still here going through this stuff.  I feel pretty fortunate to be in the pipeline group.  This group is pretty lean so hopefully, there won't be many cuts (although I am the new boy in the group).  Many of the other groups are getting pretty anxious, including our former bunch.  We should find out pretty soon.

I was in Salt Lake City a couple of weeks ago and I called Rhondo.  He is working for the IOC and is in charge of all the fund raising for the Olympic charities.  It seems to be right up his ally.  He asked me to tell you hello.

<NAME/> and I took vacation last week.  I played golf in San <NAME/> (La Cantarra - in case <NAME/> is wondering - excellent course) and also played here in <NAME/> with <NAME/>, <NAME/> and <NAME/> <NAME/>.  It was fun.

Please write back and let me know how you are doing.  How's the job, How's <NAME/>, How's LA, How was Thanksgiving...many questions.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a33.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

When: Thursday, October 18, 2001 10:00 AM-11:00 AM (GMT-06:00) Central Time (US & Canada).
Where: TBD

*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a34.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

You can send it which ever way is easiest for you.  If it is just the same, I would send his seperately.  He is located at: EB1344.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a35.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

Sounds good.  I was in <NAME/> this last week...recruiting, golf and KSU game (close).  I also picked up my tickets for this weekend.  I don't like thinking about the game, it makes me nervous but that is the fun of it.

By the way, can you tell me the line?  I'm sure you are favored.

Boomer Sooner,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a36.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Howdy!!!!

What is going on?  I heard from <NAME/> that she may have some decisions to make soon.  Are you going through the same thing?  I'm interested to know.

I heard from <NAME/> Maus last week.  He is doing some contract work for <NAME/>.  He and his family are enjoying <NAME/>.

Please call or email me.

I hope all is well.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a37.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

I spoke to him and he is here and well.  He can be reached at 713-345-9592 or greg.phillips@enron.com.  He says "Hello".

I love you.
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a38.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

When: Wednesday, November 14, 2001 1:30 PM-2:00 PM (GMT-06:00) Central Time (US & Canada).
Where: 1336

*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a39.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

yuk?  It could be perfect.  "Saturday...sunny. Highs in the upper 60s. Light southwest winds."  Although the low could be a bit chilly.
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a4.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

How's it going in Brazil?  I know you are happy to be back.

I transferred out of EBS and got back into the gas business.  I'm working for the pipeline group.  The people here are very nice and I'm glad to be back in this industry.  Although, I must say that I will miss London and working with people like yourself.

I got a message from <NAME/> Joergansen the other day.  Do you happen to know his email address?  Please let me know.

I hope all is well down south.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a40.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

I just wanted to thank you and the staff for the OU/UT tickets.  We had a great time and you know the game was exciting.

I also enjoyed meeting you two weeks ago.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a41.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

When: Wednesday, October 10, 2001 10:00 AM-1:00 PM (GMT-06:00) Central Time (US & Canada).

*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a42.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,  Attached is what I've got.

Please assign and have them contact the rep below to get the information you need.
I'll also pass on anything else I get.

Let me know who gets this project.

Thanks,
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a43.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

It sounds like you have the right attitude about the situation (I wouldn't have guessed otherwise).  The fun aspect of it is that you can do whatever you want.  Sometimes the hard thing is figuring out what that is.  I truly wish you the best and I certainly want to know where you place yourself.

Oh, I heard from <NAME/>.  They have settled in <NAME/> and he is still looking for a job but he may do some contract work for <NAME/>.  I'm not sure how definite it is or what he'll be doing.  I'll let you know what I find out.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a44.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

I have arranged to take off this Friday, so I will be able to attend.  I guess I'll get the directions to the golf course and other details from Weed and Dial.  If the teams are all full, put me on their team.  Otherwise, I'll play with anyone.  My game has gone down the tubes since I started the international work.  I hope to take care of that problem soon.....put me down as a 24 handicap.

I look forward to seeing you and the rest of the guys,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a45.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

I got out of my morning meeting and <NAME/> still wasn't in (~8:45).  I had a bad feeling.  She came in at 9:00, straight from the vet.
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a46.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

Howdy <NAME/>,

Well, your name is still on the list so that is good.  I hope all is well with you and your hubby.

Awfully weird times here in the home office.  Really strange vibes all over the building...people wondering about their jobs, sad about their retirement accounts and wonderment about how a proud (maybe too proud) Fortune 10 company could go down in ~3 weeks.  I guess it is the same or similar there too.

The pipeline group is working out.  I really like the people and am starting to get comfortable with the business and my regulated surroundings.

Please respond and let me know what you are up to and how you are doing.  I'm so sorry we didn't hook up when you were in town last time.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a47.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

Could you make sure that <NAME/> (referenced above) and I are on your distribution list for the TW Marketing team.  We just joined the group.

Thanks,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a5.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

I hope you have enjoyed your time working in Europe as much as I did.  I have recently made a switch and I left the broadband group and joined the Transwestern Pipeline Marketing team.

I'll talk to you later,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a6.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

In the next few days.  We'll call you and let you know when we start the process so we can get your imput.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a7.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

Thanks for the pics.  She is adorable!  I always enjoy getting them.

I'm heading to <NAME/> to watch the OU/KSU game.  We finally get to see how good we are.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a8.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

To follow up from our meeting today, please provide the delivery report that includes the following:

WHAT	Total volumes (by month) delivered to primary delivery points versus alternate delivery points
WHEN	For the period of 5/00 thru 10/31
WHERE	For all delivery points West of Thoreau (including: Calif pool, Window <NAME/>, PGE/Mojave Topock and SOCAL Needles)
WHO	Send to <NAME/> Rapp (legal), <NAME/> Watson and myself

This information will be used to respond to criticism by the California PUC.  I believe that <NAME/> Rapp is wanting to respond by early Wednesday so if he could get these numbers by end of day Monday, I'm sure he'd appreciate it.

Thanks for your help,

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="Verify3Train//a9.xml">
 <author id="x9971474699999111010188"/>
  <body>

Sunita,

I am planning on attending <NAME/>'s party.  <NAME/> will be out of town so i will be flying solo that night.

Let me know if I can help out by bringing anything.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

</training>
